night turns long. She rises in shadows, fierce and strong. Lilith in Scorpio, my anima, flame.
Whispers my secrets, calls out my name.
Choose to go. You chose to come here. Thank you very much
But nobody's commenting yet, so
We have some new shorts though new shorts when it's the new shorts
I don't know is it I think this did the checkie doll scare it went away
hopefully they did
I mean not mean just like scare the right people away. Let me see that I do have some shorts
Yeah, can you intervene keep an eye on it? It's a chat talk to the chat. You know what I'm gonna do
I'm gonna pull my dick y'all better not how fast skate
Like delete the clip or whatever win while you're wanting to save the video
That's all you're gonna talk about
None of your business
Okay, I can't I can't I can't leave this guy for a second. I'm gonna pull my dick out. Yeah, can you intervene?
Can you keep an eye on him?
If I remember correctly, I think the terms for peace were the beat I made a little community post
no, I
Don't remember thought was the terms. I didn't set them. It's one of our guys in the DC, you know, but I
Think the terms are just a little community post from be a and as be his friend. I'd like to
Maybe you should make the community post.
Congratulations.
be the quickest solution to all of this.
I would make a community post.
What do you think?
Just in support of her, but yeah,
you can't don't drag me into like,
no, do this, do this.
You know, it's like, I'm,
she doesn't like to be told what to do.
I don't like to be told what to do.
You know, I don't, I don't,
I really have nothing to do with the situation.
And it's like, she has a,
she has the right to make her own decision about it.
I've made my own,
I've made my own decisions.
I will make a community post on my own,
you know, supporting her and.
promoting her channel or whatever, you know, but I'm not, I'm not going to be, that's
the kind of like in China when they would say, they say, okay, right, you know, right,
they made the Americans, they caught, or Japan, Japan, they would have them like sign
these things. Now, you know, it's like, it's kind of the same thing. It feels like a kind
of a coerced kind of thing. And it's kind of makes me uncomfortable to think about, like
the,
And, you know, we all can make those decisions.
I won't be pushed around or anything.
I'm going to use the ascertaining people.
No, no, I'm saying, I'm saying, you know,
can kind of give that feeling a little bit, like where it's like,
oh, you know, things would be better.
You know, it's the kind of like, it's a little.
you know just like a little undertone of like a hostility there and it's like I'm not really
about that I'm about yeah I'm about you know having a fun supportive show positive show I'm
about supporting my friends and so whatever the decision I respect but you have to respect my
decisions like yeah I don't want to get more and if I remember correctly I think the terms for
I don't remember if that was the parents...
I didn't.
I'm gonna die one day.
Oh darling, one token of the life.
You're gonna die one day. Sorry. I didn't mean to die on your screen.
You'll help by reading.
I'm good. I'm sorry I'm died. I didn't die.
You're gonna die one day.
Who the fuck do you think you are? You're trying to like talk to me like what?
I can't be with a skinny bitch. I've been with a fucking model like growing up.
I don't give a fuck about uh size zero.
I enjoy fat bitches.
I didn't say I didn't say I just said it was I thought the story was shot
Like you put it a very very very like you think that I can't get with fucking like I never said
Looking bitches. It's like shut the fuck up. You're nobody like you can look at me
You see I look way better than any of you motherfuckers
Well, I don't think it's not
Just because I like a fucking
Well, no one said there's anything wrong.
Hey, what?
I could take your bitch.
Like any fucking bitch that any of these losers that have, I've taken her.
I don't want them.
I love fat bitches.
It's not so hard to understand.
You're so fucking stupid.
You can't understand that a guy likes fat bitch.
Fucking retard lady. You're a weirdo. Yeah
Pedophile who the fuck do you think you are you're trying to like talk to me like what I?
Can't be with a skinny bitch. I'm feeling with a fucking model like
Rolling up. I don't feel a fuck about
Size zero
Man
Anyway, so
And they can't say she's not bullying you what is bullying like if we look up the definition and the webster's dictionary
Bullying is doing something and trying to make somebody do something
against their will and make them do stuff like, you know, that's bullying
Bullying can be also like pushing people over the edge
I'm trying to destroy all of the top and then you don't need to make fun of me when I'm
alive.
Okay.
Hi, Halo!
What's up, guys?
So, I think this looks pretty good now, and I do have a green screen, I don't even know
if I need the green screen really, but this does seem to be working pretty well, I don't
know, but I think the green screen is still cool, but I want to use some special effects.
I got it. And this actually fits perfectly too. Yeah. I like this. Okay. You like this
Crustable Ghost.
Ghosty.
Oh, oh, where'd he go?
Where'd he go?
Okay, this is scary.
Hi, hello.
I don't know where everyone is.
Is there really three people here?
I don't know.
Is there someone saying terrible things about me?
I know I just came back from my spunkies chat
and it was like.
Not pretty friendly over there. It was like rain saying like oh, I have a ideas
No, I'm like, you know
Disgusting or this thing making fun. I mean then God God he put this a picture of like me. It's like
Shit coming on my mouth or something. I don't know it was like disgusting
I was like now like the picture full screen for like several minutes
I was like you just they probably take that down at the full screen picture of me like, you know
It's like really disgusting and she was just laughing and then I was like
Are you saying I was like am I gonna treat it like this wherever it's a I'm not gonna go to shows if I just get really garbage
Hey, what's up dude? Oh nice
Saw you for a second here
No, turn me show you I saw you. I saw your face a little bit
Was I beautiful? Yeah, you were you're a great track
Yeah, but I mean it wasn't that I mean it was like I know
It wasn't very nice. It wasn't very nice. I was like, you know, and they're like, they're just like, of course
I just go into it then I'm sure as I expect that they're gonna be
What's the argument by the way, so I have your back the argument is
They weren't very nice. There's no argument is like they were they weren't
Mason was there too. I mean I was just kind of joking around too, but they took it too far and it's like
It's like how basically you can see I could say the worst things ever and it's like of course
You can take in at the joke, but it's like you've done eventually if they keep saying the worst things over and over and over
It's like yeah, I could make their argument just because they weren't being very nice. There's a good argument to get with that
Yeah, yeah Sebastian's right
So I said, if you want to come up and talk to ghost and I come up to yeah, thank you
Why not join the panel why not donate a little bit to the chin you don't have to donate a lot at all
Everybody to get the troll pedia, and I only have it for like five dollars, but I did
About that for a long time and it's like so materialized
i'm just saying you can come here and talk shit to me talk shit the ghost go ahead
or sponsor a channel or
donate or
I understand like people have been like
You know, I know and it's a guy that you do want to economically ever know it's like you can just send the cash app
And by the way ghost will I will literally leave I will not try to fight that at all by the way
If you give sake if you money, I will I'll leave a hundred percent
It's been slander so much goes it's like, you know, it's like I'm not surprised that people are like
Because just with all that said about all the negativity and all those people that just really hate me
I don't slander anyone, I get more money than anyone, I know that, but I don't slander anyone
What do you mean by slander though?
Well, I mean it's like saying that I'm a bad person or I'm just spending money on drugs
Am I saying that? Or have I argued against? Have I always had your back? Ever since?
Yeah, you were very kind and it's like, but then it's also like, you know
other stuff going on too where it's like the things are getting a little bit more stressful right now
just to confirm personal life and I've never once had your back I can't sit there and have your back
what you what's you're trying to make you're trying to bully your friends right now I find
not always like that I'm not trying to do anything I just all I want all I want to do is just hang out
real time so I'm just like I just steam spare to me. I just feel like that uh people like
you know might have a negative like you can see there's not many people there.
I've always had your back though have I not I've called I've literally I've literally talked
but besides all that fuck all that I've literally debated for your back.
Yeah I've literally had your back. I don't know it's just like um
But you know what I had a great day today with that with Alex she had me on her show
We're doing it a little like check in with me day like a certain days and those like so she's kind of like
No have me on and so it's like so much fun and like so awesome
And it's like she's used me so well, but it's like when I go to somewhere
And I'm literally setting her happy for you
They like they all come in and like sort of like
Started out slow and then it's like and I was like
So I see you're gonna be real cool who you're talking to like this because I've had your back a lot
I'm not trying to talk shit, but I love you my brother
You're talking to you like that brother
What's your argument what what are you talking about was I not there you don't have your back
I
Paid money to your chat paid a lot of money actually and I always had your back voice had your you're fucking
Boys
I'm not trying to debate, okay?
I'm just trying to understand.
What the fuck are you talking about?
You better be real careful, brother.
There's a lot of people on the center that hit you,
and I'm the one that loves you.
You better remember that.
Thank you.
And then, Sebastian's right too,
is that they're really good at that.
Well, no fuck that.
You're gonna be a bitch about it.
No fuck that.
If you're gonna be a bitch about that.
Maybe not.
I was explaining what happened
right before I came to the show.
I was on Spunky's show,
and they were saying terrible things,
and it's like,
I know you I know you and I'm there defending you. You were there you were there
And what else you what else you want to do what else you might do?
Because I wasn't looking in the chat
I was I couldn't see the chat on stream york is winning or just because I'm not I'm not around every fucking
Every single post I am there the majority of the time fucking defending you you know that
Why you talking shit you can't lose a friend bro you talk a lot
I'm not talking about you. I'm talking about rain and jt and gawdy that were like
Pictures of me like shit and stuff like that and then people just talking all this shit about me. I don't know brother man
You're fucking. I don't know why you're hating on me. I've
But fuck the donation what you give me a lot of money, but fuck the donation I fucking defend you debate wise
How many times like you
I'm tired
Like if you don't actually understand what I'm saying actually like fucking
Well
Okay, I mean they guys these are like a little bit of a misunderstanding there ridiculous. He's throwing again that yeah, that's why yeah
It's just ghosts and blackouts calling the most both out like
She's human got either rude and they're critical there
Yeah, I
Can actually play this there's like a video
Yeah, I don't know what his problem is, but he was not understanding what I was trying
to say.
I was not saying anything about him, I was talking all about, I was just on Sponky's
channel.
Maybe maybe it's just like the astrologically. I'm like things are just a weird right now or something
It's like I'm not talking to a few people but and then
Maybe I'm just a big sucker and like
So I'm gonna look for sure I'm allowed to play this
Well, maybe I'm not, I don't know, I don't want to doxer or whatever.
Yeah, he was a good hit as well.
The brain was fried
I thought that I could win
But the chat just sighed
Won't you banish me
They said I wasn't reasonable
So this is the actual song that it's inspired by.
She calls the song embarrassing.
I don't think that's a good idea, I think it's funny.
So here's actual.
I don't know what she likes to talk about, but she's like, what's your favorite song that she's done?
She thinks the video's a better song.
I think it's a good song.
There's one more song I really like.
Well, I like the EP you're in buying song too, but
she has a song called
Yeah, this is a cute song. Try this.
Doesn't love me, my fiancé wants my money
My fiancé, he is starving
My fiancé's a little retarded
My fiancé doesn't need me
My fiancé's always cheating
My fiancé's with a guy named Lucas
My fiancé's full of excuses
Doesn't kiss me, my fiancé Doesn't miss me, my fiancé
Doesn't know my address Or my little name
My fiancé, he is so gay Talking about bubbles on our dates
Daddy tells me, don't worry He only fucks guys and they don't fuck it
Yeah, mafia, say, yeah, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, yeah, mafia, say, yeah, mafia, say, yeah, mafia, say, yeah, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say, mafia, say
What's going on?
Okay
It's okay
Meanwhile at the bunny ranch
Okay, I'm done. Okay, I'm done
It's a lot of bread, isn't it? It's a lot of bread.
Yeah, so I had a bad time out.
My Snapchat is going crazy.
Do you guys ever want to actually have a website where people will get back to you on it?
Because TikTok, most of the Nigerians or something like that.
But on Snapchat, everyone's getting back to me on Snapchat.
I guess people don't like, I don't know, I think there's like a backlash against me, I've got, I don't know, but you know what, it's probably people that weren't going to be vibing anyway, I think there's some people that are so fickle, you know, and then it's like, and then they'll just like, you know, just drop, drop a foot, whatever, but...
I was looking into like a watermark anyway, but so they're okay. There's double digits in the room. That's not too bad
So anyway, I made these prayer curbs too right there
you know before like
Whoever whoever
The deities these particular ones were like based on my birthday
But there's different systems, everything.
But these are Saturnian angels because no Saturn,
the Capricorn is ruled by Saturn.
And so whatever planet rules you're assigned,
will probably be some angels to look at.
But there's also like 72 angels in the Kabbalah
that have different properties.
They're basically all a combination of three letters,
three Hebrew letters.
And so that's how I learned the Hebrew alphabet.
I'm studying that, but uh, that one's not even, pretty cool, huh?
Meat's Rail, um, see it, but, and also I have like a lot of,
like, I do have a lot of the uh, the leaflet in my chart,
I have like several planets in it, including Saturn, Jupiter,
I have Saturn, Jupiter, and Pluto, all in a meagre in the ninth house.
So I have a lot of the scale of the justice, not going to think of close up pointing to
the justice in my chart.
And this one has the hourglass and the key.
These are also like big symbols for me, but yeah.
this one sounds like the serenity prayer which is like really big ironically I just had the
serenity prayer in my mind I always have it it's like one of the best prayers you know
give me the wisdom to understand uh the wisdom to to know or know what I can change the wisdom to
know what I can't change and for the wisdom to know that I don't have to get the first
But this is pretty similar.
Grant me the strength to endure patients to grow
and wisdom to understand.
This is like things to give yourself to.
You can give it to other, higher self in a way,
or like some kind of like the light, you know?
It's like in the light, all, just like light,
you know, it's all the same light.
Okay, so anyway.
So I hope you liked the, I fit up a lot of shorts.
The garb is super, I mean, it's like,
It's hard to get too many of them.
Like, on StreamYard, I'm allowed to get the short,
if the stream is like under two hours,
but it's hard to do that.
And I think, I look back, I have so many streams
that are so long, I don't know why I'm so fired for now.
Yeah, there's Alexander here.
Yeah, there's Alexander's channel.
Yeah, make sure you subscribe to how he does it.
Up.
Yo, hold on.
Hey, boy.
Hey, psych.
Why didn't you defend me over there? You didn't have my back?
Yeah, it was like, listen, why were you telling me that you want to be gay and stuff like that?
In case you wanted to try it one time.
But I thought you knew I was never gay though. I was always a straight guy.
Did you say you never had, but you didn't have a mate with me?
Remember you said that last thing you said you didn't know, you said you had to think about it, you thought about it and you said no.
Yeah, but Syke, I thought men and women are supposed to be together when it comes to that, not like another guy with another guy.
Well, yeah, but have you heard of like there's, it wasn't Adam and Eve, it was Adam and Steve.
Oh, it wasn't Adam and Eve, it was Adam and Eve, not Adam and Steve.
You know, if it was Adam and Steve, then they probably wouldn't have kids, or I'm sure they wouldn't have, um, oh, there you are.
So, do you want to have kids?
It's like, you got to explain to me, though, man.
Like, I don't completely understand, like, why you want me, though, like, and stuff like that.
Because you're so hot.
Yeah, but why do you like me so much, though? You just like me?
Yeah, like, your voice and, like, how funny you are, and, like, you're always, like, nice and smiling and, like, kind.
Yeah, but it's like well, I was just trying to tell you I was never gave them my whole life
I haven't been like that way
Never you never like, you know, like had like a fantasy of like being in the locker room and like
Making love in the shower. I
Heard I heard people talking about it before but I just never done it
I don't know why I just never had that I never had that kind of like thoughts. I never thought that way
Yeah, but yeah, but how would how would I know if like if I like I'm out
Yeah, I don't know if I like that close your eyes bend over and
I'm just I know I know you can be the top you can be on top. I'm sorry. I'm just kidding
I'm just kidding. It was a joke. It was like psych. So I don't get it like what made you think like this door
What made you want to be this and what made you want to think this way?
You're like you're like Edward Norton in that American history X through six. So it's a good looking
Sikes like so what do you think about me though, man?
You think you think I'm a cool guy that I'm psyched like you think I'm
No, I really don't want to get I'm just kidding. I don't want to get married. I don't want to get married, but
Do you want to come live with me?
If not gay, we just are going to share the same bed,
have sex once in a while, and live together.
So why haven't you found anybody else, though?
Like, why do you want to choose me, though?
I was waiting for you.
Are you sure it's me that you really want, though?
I mean.
Yeah.
I mean, I was like, I always wanted to meet him.
Here you are.
It's like so you can't you really you really don't want to just be friends though
You want to what be really just can't be just friends
Friends with benefits
You're saying you want to be with friends with benefits. Yeah
It's hard for me to it's hard for me to
Start for me to figure that out though. It's like if I want to do that
Okay, well, just think about it and let me know
You have to change your mind, but you know, I'm always here.
So like, I gotta think about stuff like this, yeah.
Yeah, but I mean, you've had a couple of weeks. I mean, it's like how long do you need it?
It's just, I can't figure this out, man, because I've never been through stuff like this before.
Yeah, well, yeah, it's the first time for everything including gay sex, right?
It's like, so I don't know what to say, man.
Would you try it would you just try it would you have a how just making out we don't have sex
So like you just want to see what it would be like. Yeah
Oh
I mean, it's hard. I mean, I don't know the um, I
Don't know things might things might come your way and stuff like that. It's like you never know
Yeah, like you
You're talking about me. Yeah
Yeah, you never know. It's like you just got to wait and see man. That's the false hope ever
that my whole life people meet me in New Falls. He's never gonna come out of here. He's never gonna stay with me. Wait what?
You're never gonna, you're never gonna, you're never gonna, you're never gonna try it with me.
It's like why am I never gonna?
Yeah, it's like why am I never gonna try it with you?
Because you said you're a straight guy and you're not interested at all and it's like you just want to be friends.
It's like my whole life. It's like a lot of my life. I've been this way though
Just all just mostly into my you know, I've been friends with guys, but not really you know gay
I just never been gay. I don't I don't know
Not really or definitely not like I like you like what have you done stuff?
What's the most what's the gayest thing you've ever done?
I've slept in the same bed with a guy but that was like at a group home when I was with other guys because all they
Had was guys that in the same place
Did he like reach you over the middle of the night and give you a hand job I?
Just felt I just felt like when I was with my friends there at the group home
I could lay in the same bed with them
But I would get caught by the person that owns those group homes and I'll get in trouble for doing stuff like that
I wasn't trying to get in trouble though doing that though before we joined the bed
I was laying with other guys when everybody's supposed to be in their own separate bed that they had there
Because I felt better better being with somebody next to me and stuff like that
Yeah, I just needed some company or something like that site that's all I'm trying to say yeah, I understand that I can do some company too yeah like
Hey, hey, hey, Tracy. Hey, come on up, Tracy, if you can't hold on, you see, and I think Paige might be coming later.
Are you ever at Paige Mesa?
I don't know who that is.
Prairie Paige from Canada, you ever met her? She's awesome.
So, like, have I ever talked to her before, or she's someone I've ever talked to?
I've been around for a little while, so I don't think you have, because you've only been on my show for a couple weeks, but...
So she's a psycho
Like why were they talking about my hair being bald and stuff like that or I was balding on my hair
I don't think my hair is balding. You just have like a like a large forehead. It's not balding
It's like it just kind of like has that illusion. I get my head like my head looks like I look like I'm balding, right?
Yeah, it's just like but these were just for my horns used to be used to be like a
Kind of horned so I saw so why did you go on? Why did you go on sponky's channel, though?
I never saw you on that panel before
I went there. I thought I would go there to see hi and have a nice time, but
Everyone just felt like ganging up on me and teasing me and like
What no what what?
It's like why did you put up a book?
Why did you put up a book called like a truck trolls or something like that troll of media or something like that?
Yeah troll media
This is my new book, hold on, I'll put it up for a second.
It's available on PsycheAwayGiddens.com.
It's called Trollpedia.
And yes, it is all about YouTube trolls and all kinds
of interesting things.
And also remedies for everything, too.
There's also some surprises in the book.
The book will evolve.
It is $5 on PsycheAwayGiddens.com.
So you can check that out, but yeah, I plan on making it actually expanding it and making it
Even more of an amazing
So like so what is that book about though? It's just about trolls or something or what's that about?
Yeah, it's about what's about like, you know, so like this is me
they get that character is based on me and
and basically, you know, I'm a little bit of a troll but not like on
Purpose is just like I just did genetically like a little bit, you know
I might have a goblin or something in my ancestors some place and so why did you why would you make a book about that though?
Because I want to help people know first be aware of it because it's like when I started streaming
Especially this is good for a few start for streamer because it will have good advice
But like you know how to handle things and streaming because when I started I didn't really know about porn bombs
The first time I saw a porn bomb was like on beat us and like I've never seen that before like on it anywhere
And I was like but it's like a minute. It's just like part of the part for the course like on her show
I mean it happens happens to most live streamers, right?
Um, but yeah, it doesn't happen on Tik Tok really.
It doesn't really happen.
It just happens on YouTube.
It's like a phenomenon on YouTube really.
And it's like, there's like, yeah, I was going to say.
So what do you, what do you think about, wait, why, why did you say
porn bombing?
Cause people do that on, they're hard to, people that they do that
and stuff like, right?
I'm all the time.
Yeah.
I've been home over a hundred times.
It's like, it's like basically like a war zone over here.
But, but you know what?
I've actually been able to, to not ever get in trouble.
Most of the time I did not get in trouble for,
I was able to get them down in time.
So yeah, I would really appreciate you guys
if you could check out the book
and it's only $5, I traced it so everyone can check it out.
And it also supports the bill and it'll be basically
not unless you know, I will know.
So yeah.
So you made this book yourself though
or who wrote this book?
I wrote the book.
You wrote that book yourself?
Yes.
And when it's just it's just about people that are yeah, I can read a little bit of it
Like let's see your book. Okay. Yeah, it's just about trolls like is that what it's about though, or you got basically YouTube trolls
It's more specific to YouTube
Okay, yeah, I have see it's fully illustrated
Okay, it goes into the top 10 breeds of YouTube trolls. We can go for example. Let's have a look
So we can look at some of the tags on YouTube scrolls, but there are the drive by Heckler.
It says, I was, I was, let me see, I'm going to take off my glasses, I'll take these ones
off.
I was the mosquito of the chat room.
Quick sting, quick exit, Korean L, ratio, short words, like a flicked pebble at your window.
The point was not conversation.
It was interruption.
Blink, and I was gone.
But it's remained regret, maybe, by admit.
There was an elegance to how little effort it took to ruin somebody's mood.
There was the edge of the road. Nothing was sacred.
Tragedy struck. I joked about it. There was pain. I poked at it.
I told myself I was breaking taboos. But really, I was just numb.
Regret burns here. It wasn't a bravery. It was cowardice, hiding behind cruelty.
So, I'm ready from the point of view as a troll, because I'm a royal troll, right?
I'm like...
It's like...
Yeah.
It's like, so what is the definition of a troll, though?
Are you telling me that, or no?
Yeah, see, that's me right there.
And I can't...
I'm showing too much of the book.
There we go.
What is the definition of a troll?
A troll is basically somebody that lives under a bridge and, you know...
They
They on the internet they just hurt their ass you there's a lot of things that fall under the umbrella of troll
I would include stalkers in that now. I would include like
Some psychopaths and narcissists that mean
Anybody who gaslights the trolls love to gaslight and all kinds of and that's another thing. It's like that's another thing
What is gaslight? What is gaslight about?
Okay, so Gasly was a movie from like the 1930s or something with Ingrid Bergman
And it was about this woman that inherits like all this money from her aunt and she goes to like, you know
Collect the money and like live at this like her aunt's like house or whatever starts eating a guy
And he starts to try to make her think that she's going crazy because he wants to get her like put away in a mental asylum
So he can like keep her house or money and stuff. So it's kind of like
It's like, but basically in that time period they didn't have electricity,
I remember the time period was a movie, they didn't have electric lamps, they had these gas
light bulbs, and so he would fuck with the gas in the other room, and so flicker on and off,
and she'd be like, I think it was a ghost or something like that, or she thinks she was going
crazy, and then she'd ask him, do you see the lights flickering, and he'd be like, no I don't see the
lights flickering, and so she would just think that she's going crazy, because he's fucking with her
Like so you tell me so it's like you're telling me that's what that's what
Trolls about or wait. I forgot. I'm saying they're gaslighters. They can be flying monkeys
They can be just people that are just like, you know, just wanting to
to irritate people and
Just basically a lot of them they're vampires
They they're like second vampires that get up on the energy the pool like the reaction
Of the people that's been loaded narcissists you with a gun narcissists right on this like
the emotional fuel, the reaction that comes out of the person and then the nurses like
sets it all up.
So what is, so like what is the death like, I know you're telling me this but I'm just
trying to say like, can you give me an example?
Sure, I was showing you the book, like there's all the examples of trolls, there's the trolls
that will porn bomb, there's the trolls that will come on and to say the N-word, and that
try to get the channel thinking about it, there's trolls that will come in and be conspiracy
theorists, there's the trolls that will come in and say terrible things and then all these
You know it's supporting the person when it's actually just all the same person they say oh, yeah, that's right
That's right, but it's all same person, right?
That's why I like sometimes when one person disappears a lot of people
Wait site, it's like wait hold on. I'm trying to say try to say give me example like guess lighting
They're like what exactly like this guess like
Well, one thing that people will do is like they'll try to like get you real upset those days
Real triggering stuff and then finally they'll trigger you and you'll get mad and maybe you'll yell and they'll be like
Well, you're acting crazy
Like wow, it's like you're so emotional and they're like trying to put you in that state, right?
And so yeah one example there's also like just like just like when you don't when you
Argue with somebody's sense of their own reality like if you're that's going to gaslight in a way
Unless it's like really true that you don't agree with it
It's like as they are fucking with their sense of their own reality like and like saying and negating it
They could say the sky is blue. You're like, no, it's green
That's like, you know, negating their reality, like saying that there's something like often about them, but it's like really, so it's like, so it's like, you're saying gasoline has to deal with somebody being triggered or something like that.
Is that what you mean?
Well, they're, they're recently trying to, um, they can be cognitive dissonance, like drive you a little bit crazy, like, like, kind of like, because it puts you on like questioning your own sense of reality.
place in your head where you're, where you're easily like,
full to one side or the other, right? It's like, you need to,
yeah.
I never heard of such thing, though. So, like, that's why I'm trying to figure this
up. I mean, I don't know. I mean, I've only had to deal with you. I mean,
they're, they're, they're, they're relatively rare in society, but I mean,
it's like, but then, it's like, they're,
They have like a bigger presence than the percentage would say it's like you would think that they're just like 1%
So one out of 100 they're celebrated in all these movies as a anti hero
There's also just like a lot of them in certain industries that goes so there's higher percentages in certain places
Like you'll see in Hollywood. There's probably a huge amount of sites. Yeah
Did you ever get a last video that I showed you but I think we won off like last time I showed it to you like
Yeah, I was really just kidding. Can you show it to me though? Like can you show me what it looks like like?
There's no nudity. I thought you were gonna send me a second video and it was just like you at the drums and some store
Okay
Yeah, but me
Yeah, you're gonna send me a sexy photo. Okay, so here you are
Wait, what do you mean like psych? What do you what do you mean send you the?
Like, you know what right you like it's like the dick dick or something I?
Thought you I thought you don't want I thought you don't want stuff like that
No, I only want stuff like that
It's okay
Like what you told me stuff like it's like I mean, I don't really do this either
But I thought you said you don't really like that anybody to porn bomb you and stuff like that
No, I don't I don't I mean that's not it's not for me if you do it off the like, you know
I got you know
Right like not
You have a second
You tell me to show you like my body stuff like that, but that's I thought that's the same thing as form on me
No, but it's not if you just show it. If you show it like, you know, off of like off of the show
It gives you know, you're emailing, right?
Yeah, yeah
And so guys, I'm also gonna do a course on
Patrols and like control management and even though it's a
I am a good, I do deal with trolls well if you can see what I've been through, but it's like
Yeah
Um, I just don't I don't know if I feel comfortable though like what doing
You're gonna try one time?
I just I just never done stuff like that
It's not like too different from a, I can like, I can get like a wig and like lipstick and then like turn off the lights
And then you only know the difference, right?
Wait, so like can you show me that did you ever find that video I sent you?
Yeah, I don't think it was opening for
These did you did you still get it though the video? I got it for sure. I
Don't think you ever seen it though, right? It was like when I showed you when you got offered
You're like in like a drum store that one where you're the drum store
Did you see that or what I thought were you in the drum store? How would I know you're in the drum store?
I didn't see it what I was gonna say. Did you see me play in the drums though? Or what did you see?
You're playing the drums
Was it a video?
Yeah, it was a video or that one was a video and then there was another video and you're like looking at the camera cross-eyed a little bit
Psych there's me one playing on the drum so right it's on that. Yeah, it was that you're in a drum store, right?
Yeah
Yeah, I agree I agree
So I look at side you still got it though. Like can he show it? Well, I'm looking at my email. Okay, so let me see
Non-new photos
As a disappointing photos of Mason
Because you're a fluke. I need to go to my
I don't know, I saw two, I saw only two messages in the email, I don't know why it's, like, not showing everything.
Um, they're mason.
Okay, oh here it is, okay. It says...
I don't know, I can't, it's hard, it's not really behaving right now.
It's like, what is it though? Is it like a video? Yeah
Okay, I'll try to open it right here. Oh
It's a good it's a YouTube. Okay. I can copy it copy. I'll show it on the I'll throw it to you on the screen
So I can you play it for me to like can you show it like I'm doing it right now
Oh
It's like yeah, it's like it's turning blurry though. I can't really see though
Were you did you see it? Did you see another one though?
This is your channel like that one of them
Are you doing here?
Everything about me
It's like what is that? It's you isn't it?
So like is that me? I think so
Is it so I got looks like like that looks like me man. Thank you. Thank you. Yeah
So like you like that
Yeah
What do you like about it? It's like what do you like about it?
You like that
It's like that's interested right that's interesting. What are you doing here? Just sitting there in the camera
Do you want another video site? Do you want another video?
Are you gonna be naked in it?
What do you want to see though?
everything
No, you don't have to send it
I know this is the same as with the imagination. I want to see it. I want to see it up in person
So I can you put can you put the thing in the back chest so I can send you a video for my email? Yeah
You know send me a dick pic. What do you want though? Well, yeah, you can say that. I won't yeah, I won't show anybody else
Like what do you want to see man?
Yeah, just like show it to whatever you feel comfortable showing you can just like do it like over the pants
See the outline
Oh, guys, what am I gonna get?
Am I gonna get a, are you taking a picture now
or do you have one saved?
You send them to women?
We have a guest.
Tony, me, folks, how are you doing, sonny?
Good, how are you tonight?
Last morning here, mate, hope to see ya.
Good morning and good night.
It's not letting me sin because it's saying to follow is too big and stuff like that.
Well, let me send it.
Because your penis is too big.
So it's like saying like...
Sike, I don't get what's going on with it.
It's too big for the email.
Just hit the...
Show it to me later, okay?
We'll talk on the phone maybe you can show it to me.
We're backstage.
We'll do a freak off.
Perfect.
Yeah.
Rwy'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl i'n meddwl
Yeah, I just wanted to hop up and say hello, it's nice and quiet here, you know, this is a garbage which is too long on other channels, and I thought, do you know what, I need some peace, I thought I'd make it here, because you like it.
Well, I can't with, like, you know, friendly people, like, but, like, uh...
Yeah. Yeah, you need time to chill, like, you need time to chill.
I went to somebody's chat tonight, like, to have a good night's time, and then it's, like,
I just got, like, attacked, like, terribly.
It was bad as you could be attacked by somebody, and, like, I was expecting to go like this, like...
Psyche!
Yeah.
Why did they tell you all about this weird stuff, like, today, though?
Psyche, when you went to their street...
What were they saying, Mason?
Tell everyone what they were saying.
They're talking about my hair they're talking about my hair being bald at the top of my head
Like I don't get why it's like I don't get why they're talking about my hair being bald on the top of my head when I'm not involved in
All right, so you've got a receding hairline so what so good?
You know, it's part and parcel of life
Some people get it early some people get it late
Yeah, and trolls love to make fun of like things that are like, you know, you can't help, like you can't help with your hair.
I've had my trolls in the past, and this is why I say you don't need to worry about trolls.
Trolls have got nothing else to do in their lives other than try and pick on people just for the sake of it, you know.
Don't worry about them.
So, you know, and even when they start to attack you, just ignore them because they're the losers in life, not you.
I mean, I agree. I agree. It's just like, there's like, I think nowadays it's going beyond just trolling, it's going into like, just like a criminal territory, actually, like where it's like...
Yes, I agree. And I call one just...
How's it going in the criminal activity though? It's like your activity by when people dox people and they harass people
when they stalk people when they
You know or do worse they do worse things too
Or just like you know
even smear campaigns and
destroyer reputation destroyer destroyer of
all kinds of like things that basically
You wouldn't think are real things, but it's like they there are real things like so, you know
It's like yeah things, but it doesn't tell us the person that's feeling things, right?
So it's like but why were they arguing so much so they kept going back and forth with each other
It's just their personalities. They just like to argue and fight that is this chaotic
I'm just like done with done with the negativity. She was saying like I had eight Aids and like
Um, they were putting a pictures of me up like they were discussing and like putting a month full screen and stuff like that. It's like
I was like wow, I well if I'm gonna treat it like this, I'm not gonna like
I wanted to be friendly. All these appearances have been a disaster, except for my appearances
in Alexander. Those have been wonderful. But at any other show I go on, they're a super
disrespectful, rude, and unkind, and not very awry for me, though.
Anyway, if only people knew the real you and saw the real you they'd probably realize that you mean no harm to anybody
But they wouldn't be trolls
Right, I mean it's like there's nothing and the trolls like you won't let you win
That's the thing. It's like they're writing the rules themselves
I mean
Well, I'm not I just like healthy conversations like you know
Yes, I'm no troll right site. I don't know you might be a little bit of a troll
I think you're like
You're there you know like wait, you know, you're like you're like pretending to be kind of like you know innocent
I think you're not as innocent as you look. No, it's like I am innocent though. I'm not really a troll, but okay
Everyone has like a little bit of trouble with everybody, we're like human beings or we're mixed with like mermaids, trolls, and leprechauns, fairies, and all kinds of mythological creatures are all part of our even theological makeup, right?
No psych, I know how to be good, I know how to behave for most of the time.
Most of the time, but when you misbehave what do you do?
Well, I don't really misbehave. I mean really at all
No, not that much. I mean, I'm usually just doing my own thing and stuff like that
Huh
You are 99.9% perfect in every way shape and form. I don't believe it
No
What what do you say site
No, I'm mostly yeah, I mean, I don't know if I want to say more than mostly because I usually just I'm usually just a good guy man
I behave pretty much
Of a trespass somewhere like going somewhere. What's it supposed to be?
Yeah, trust us before it's like, yeah
Yeah, I'm practically trespassing out
It's not very bad me
YouTube in the way of being bad
I'm late. Oh, it's like
No, it's like I never really know like I really never did anything wrong on YouTube
But people will call me, you know, like a troll if we're just for no reason and they call me like I'm a AI
They call me AI or they call me a bot and stuff like that and that stuff's not true at all
You're not you swear you're not a bot you swear
Yes, like I'm sure. Hey, is that rain rain? You have to type in chat
Prove is you or you like type in the back. I don't know
I'm really fast at this, you watch this.
We'll see how it goes.
Hello?
Ah!
It was a form bomb.
Yeah, you could be careful, you know.
Especially if you try to drape it to us.
Not like I wanted to have Aztec right on the show anyway,
but, you know, I don't know what Dad would do.
I think that's like a big, like,
oh, hold it right in front of me.
I mean, I would have, but.
The only time I've ever trolled someone and it's it was recent and I'll be totally open and honest about this
I found out that somebody was a PDF in the community
over here and I
Trolled them to find out more information then put it out and then had a three-hour
Open panel about it
Everybody has that ability to troll is how you use that, right? And if you use it for good, you can't really beat the troll
right difference
No
People out there who troll because they've got nothing better to do in their lives
Yeah, they pick on people for no reason. Yeah, they have no respect
A lot of times it won't be like it won't deserve it because there's like because the trolls or like the psychopaths and
narcissists are going to be drawn to like either like good hearted people or people that are like trusted people
that have that are very familiar with their tactics and things like that.
And he tries to gaslight you to draw you into their little world so that you react
and if you can get over that and not fall into their trap
and look after these little trolls and make sure that they're comfortable at the end of this show
and you put the blanket back over them and you put them back underneath the bridge
and you say the answer, you know, you ask them to knead anything and then you just fuck up and leave them.
I'm actually like, you know, I'm like, I'm a capricorn, so I'm related to the Billy Goats Grubb, you know, there's your Billy Goats Grubb, you gotta start with Billy Goats Grubb.
it's like the baby go-go's and like he's like well I have a brother come in you
know eat the brother because it's troll so the troll let's the baby one go and
then that's the medium-sized one and they're like oh my brother is real big
you know you can eat my brother and then it's like the big go comes and you know
lots you know lots about the zodiac and the meaning of different things I'm in
Do you think I'm a typical Aries?
Well, you know, I mean, I haven't seen the temper like I would I would associate a temper with the areas love
And it's like I do like say like, you know, you're I think there's a passion you have
I guess like this fiery passion you have which is areas areas are also like the babies of the zodiacs
So they can't be crying baby sometimes they also like you relate to the young and things like that
and
You know areas are also, you know, there's she they're not too different than
They're not too different from goats or they're kind of like
I'm going to go. I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I'm going to go, I
Well, what do you what whatever you wanted to
That's me what within the you know lines, you know of like, you know, yeah, I don't know. I'm allowed to kiss you
Is that what you like me? Yeah
It's really up to you, man
Okay, well, let's do it
Sike Sikes what happened?
He had to go
What why did he leave though?
Yeah, I think he had a lip picking him up or there's I heard the dog bark now
I don't know what was going on in his background. Oh, you got a little uncomfortable with the gay conversation. I'm not sure
but it's like I was gonna say
It's like I was gonna say
I want to let me send you a big file,
like when I send it to your Gmail,
it says it can't send because the file is too big
and stuff like that.
I feel like too many gigabytes,
I think it has to be, you can like share it,
like just share it, like if you put it in the Google,
something, and you can say share,
and then I can go do it or something.
How do I do that though?
It's like, show me how to do that.
You have Google Photos?
Huh?
Yeah, okay, so go to Google Photos and then go to the video there and then
Press share and then you can never you can send it to my email. Oh
That's how you do it. It works better that way. Yeah, so then you don't have to send the whole file
You just just
Quantum get quantum guard gate in you are Vicky. I know you're Vicky. Okay. I recognize her
I know you're trying to give me the turn straight so that she can sweep me up.
Nice try Vicky.
I see.
I can tell the energy of Vicky or CB from a mile away.
So are you excited, Mason, that we're going to get married and stuff?
and follow a psyche
Mason
Lou sorry
So it's like a cycle. So how do you how do you send it man? Just don't show me how to send it
Okay, you go share is there like a someone that the share on it
Yeah, but I don't know how to send it to your email though. How do I send it?
Well, you press share and then we'll say like there's a like
Gmail somewhere
Or just can you get a link?
Is there a link?
Then you can just email me the link.
Yeah?
Oh, are you there?
He's doing that.
It's like.
Yeah.
So how do I send it?
What do I do?
Then you just say, you go share,
and then you put in my email address in the Gmail.
Did you get it though?
Sorry, did you get it? Yes, I just got it. Hold on
Yeah
Dicks and fish tacos excepted my father because I accidentally
Oh, I said the favorite person dick and fish tacos, which is my troll
Not my troll account, but somebody else truly. I'm okay. So maybe like show me what I'm showing you man
Okay
Who's that?
Who's that person?
Hello
Mason
There's fire. Oh, what yeah, are you the devil fly disappears like
Yeah, so like where's the where's the video? I don't see a video. I just see a picture
Oh, that's you hold on
Okay, here we go, I don't I mean it looks blank. Oh, I don't know if there's I don't know if it has anything on it
You didn't
attach anything
So like how do you attach it you said share or well, yeah, you have to like share or copy the link at least
How do you copy the link though?
You have to go like right click on it and go save ads or copy and then paste it
Okay, I don't know like hold on site. Yeah, I mean I mean it's a little bit a little bit like
Turn a blog. Yeah, the JTSC in your reading. There's an entity. Oh, please evil wrong McDonald's. I don't I know who that is
It's the Russian black. I'm black Russian God. Yeah, please. I know you're fucking bullshit
idiot
I'm gonna start hiding people
No, the JT has seen it. How would JT know anything first of all? JT's all into Satanism, right?
So is it
Sorry, yeah, sorry. Did you get the attachment now? Did you see what I test me look me look?
Okay, I got it. You got it. Can you can you look watch it? Yeah
What do you see you see you see like a video playing
There site site, can you watch it though? Yeah, hold on
Downloading it. Oh, here you go here. Look
This is you like look look site site site site look at it site. Do you see me on the drums?
Is that you on the drums? Yeah, that's me site. That's me on the drums. Yeah
Oh my gosh, the game is...
So like, can you see it or hear it?
Yeah, I see it. I see it on the screen. I'm watching on the big screen.
There you are.
There's volume, let me see.
Oh, I hear it.
Hear it?
Yeah.
So like, is it still playing?
What do you think about that? It's like you like it or what do you think about sexy? I love it. I love it rock star
You want to see it one more site? Can I show you another one? Yeah?
He's not good not bald. He's just
I do too
Okay, sending me some more
Sure
You guys I think this is why pie pie would get mad at me pies like don't make it AI of me
And this doesn't even look like her, here.
Or it doesn't look like me very much either.
Sike, Sike, look at what I sent you, man.
Okay.
Let me have a look, let me see it.
Oh, here it is, okay.
Mason like that you like that like that.
Wow, Mason, you showed me something.
Oh, oh, my gosh.
Are you going to show me everything?
Oh, you're turning around.
And so I was like, what do you think, man?
Yeah, I like it.
He's cute.
Guys, look, guys, like he is cute.
Look, he's not showing you.
They're cutie is
Ethan are you looking
I like it
It's like I said I said another one too. That's not the only one I sent you. It's like I sent you another one
We did all the other guy one second
Do you see the other one site? Yeah, I'm pulling it up right now. Oh
You're making you're you're doing
A nest
What do you think what do you think about that site?
Are you a Satanist
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna go and do that tonight.
You're gonna what, Sike?
Boom.
Like that.
Sike, why'd you say this guy sounds, Sike, why'd you say this guy sounds de-minted?
Who said something like that?
Apparently it's kids though. Apparently it's kids. It's a print again parent
What is that on your chin though, Mason? I
Don't have anything on it. So I guess my facial hair. Oh
It's a beer
It's a beer. You can look like Fred Durst a little bit
Do you sing nookie you know song nookie? I
Heard it song before yeah, I did it all for the nookie
So you can take that cookie
Uh-oh. Here we go. We have a guest. Let's welcome Sebastian to the show. Do you know Seb?
Huh?
Yeah, Patrick. It's me.
It's like what?
Hi, this is Seb. Do you remember him from the Spunky Show?
I don't remember.
He was on the panel.
Thank you. Thank you for support those about that. I know that was very nice of you to like yeah
That's what I was trying to tell you Patrick. They're they do that to everyone. I've seen them do it to everyone on every stream
No, they're not nice man, they're they're only lying and they're they're hypocrites and that they play dumb man
And they they're actually mean people man. They're not kind people and they're very dumb people actually
So that's why you have to like this
Acting like what man? I actually had your back and then and you act a dumb man. I think you're playing games with me
I don't think I'd like you man. I don't think I like you anymore
So I said he's I don't know what you thought about
I don't think I like you anymore Mason. I don't like the people that played dumb with me
I'll tell you that he's amazing. I tell you they think that you're pretending to be so innocent like you're really like
Like a control
No, he's playing. He's playing. He's playing people. He's been playing us man. He played me earlier
Mason you played me earlier man like you played others man come on
I actually offered you my friendship and then you played done with me. What's wrong with you now?
It's like I never did anything like that
He did to me and then he did to sake it
It's like he's making a step up. Don't believe him. It's like
Well, who put you up to it Mason just admit it. It's JT and Gaudi and rain that puts you up to that, right?
No, nobody put me up to anything
I don't think you're that dumb, and I think you're you're trying to pretend to be dumb. I think you're smarter than you yet
Here guys, you know you just this is really cool
So, TripKick did a video, let me see if I can, I need to, shit, hold on, I have to say streamer, okay, okay, I need to get the, you guys, yeah, this just came out, this is the part two of this other video, I need to show you guys real quick because this is about me, and we'll see if, it's interesting, I haven't seen this yet, yeah, it looks like,
Yeah, you want to see this real big Mason wait, you just watch a little bit. Nice. Um, I'll just say I thought you had my back
It's just like like what's going on? I do. Oh, what the fuck? I was everyone saying on their back. I do
He's just like you just throwing
You're the second person to say that
Of course Patrick they're throwing that's why I've been trying to tell you earlier
All right, let me put it on here we go
Wow crazy shit tonight, so first of all
Now be the be the be the be the
It's like we never had a problem with each other ever before man, so I don't see what's
What's going on beta?
But I also played some episodes back and it's like I didn't remember
How mean she was like and I because I thought like I was like she was really nice until like May but
She wasn't she was mean
Like she was saying like
Mean things and I was like remember when I used to go disappear off the show
like hours
It's like I was like this associated like they don't even remember like that really I
Would have done anything for I mean I love
And it's so sad like I wish I was like still
But she's so mean now it's like
And it's like not just like you know because she's she has a sweet side right, but it's like the mean side is
mean
like
Um, cruel, addictive, um, and just this stuff, like, I can't believe she was saying some
of the stuff she was saying tonight.
Basically it's seen you, I don't know, I'm gonna repeat it, but basically, you know,
she was asked about, you know, oh, you know, even, you know, had a lot of relationships,
like five, five exes or something.
And she's like, she's like, yeah, and like one of them was murdered.
And like, oh, he was with me, but you know,
it was after we divorced, but she's like,
you know, what happened?
And she's like, you'll never figure it out.
And I was like, she said, it's serious.
And I was like, and I lived in like, yeah, it was a joke.
But then after tonight, she's like, oh yeah, I had to call
clumsy and he said he's going to take care of,
if anybody bothers me from Texas, he's in a,
Okay, that's me in that, yeah,
you can go watch Tripkix video.
That's where I'm from man. I'm from Texas. You are hey
What's like the part of Houston, I mean the part of Texas I'm from is Houston that's where I'm from
Okay
Yeah
Can we write you want to write a bull?
Bull do you want to do that? Yeah?
Okay. Yeah, that's not that's something you find fun cycle. Is that why you want to do that?
Can I write bear back with you?
Yeah
Psych that's all I want to explain something to you here real fast think about it when I was on the stream earlier
And I was talking to spunky and Mason was there before rain came on everything was fine
But you notice that that one rain and Gotti and JT go on a panel everything goes wrong and they mess things up for everyone
They do that to every stream now. What's the thing that that keeps coming back? It's the same pattern
I'm not talking about you Mason. I'm talking about the JT and rain and Gotti
It's a scene do that. Can you let me talk to men for a second? It's the same pattern. Yes, you notice that Patrick
And I you know what I told that I told the Stephanie I told her spunky
I told her I said I told you about these guys there
They're troubled their problems and they're gonna mess your stream up just like they did to every other stream
They got nothing else to do. That's what they do. They go to every stream. They don't got lives. They don't work
You know that I try to explain to you Sebastian. You're saying the right stuff. That's what I'm saying. Oh, yeah
That's what it is Mason. That's what they do. They got no lives
They got no no self-respect for the for themselves. So they go and mess up other people's streams
You know, they try to cause problems to people
Yeah, but I was just trying to be normal the whole time Sebastian in that stream. I'm being serious
Well, that may be so I don't know man. I don't know you enough
But I just I don't trust anyone right now, but I'm just saying that that's what they do and they did it this spunky
That's Stephanie girl. She's the girlfriend of my friend Justin. I told them I said watch out for these people
I said you're gonna remember. I told you that in a few weeks
But then she doesn't get it. She allows me to do it
She lets them put a picture of Patrick on a stream like that. That was totally disrespectful. That wasn't right
I don't know why she let it happen. I don't know why she did that Patrick
You know, that's I think that's not right her to for her to let that happen
Well, yeah, but it reminds me of kind of like my people will get mad at me because they're like, oh you didn't
Maybe I didn't like it's like when I'm on a panel like that
I see like she's being quiet like almost endorsing it or like kind of like no encouraging it
And it's like hopefully I never did that in the past or like, you know, maybe you'll feel like that
Because that's a bad feeling and stuff. I would like because she was like putting that stuff full screen and stuff like that
Like yeah, she'd let it happen. She even did it on purpose. What the heck she leaves the picture on for like a minute
I saw that was on call for I didn't I expect I didn't expect that for her to do that
You know to be honest. I'm disappointed with her
Yeah, but I never even saw those people my whole life that I was my first time ever talking to those people are even seeing those people on there
Come on, how do I know if you're not lying to me again? I show before I saw you on the show like
Sebastian I was on that show before but those people I never talked to those people before until today
Remember I was telling you that that rain told you that you were bald. I was stuck
I was taking up for you then you were playing dumb you're saying that I was saying that you're bald
I said no, I'm defending you saying that you're not bothered. You still got hair
But I figured out I I caught on that you were playing dumb and you were playing games with her you're playing games on me with her
No, I never said that so I bet I never said that you said that I was bald or anything like that
I was just bringing up that I wasn't bald. That's all was bringing up earlier. I don't know man
I don't know if you're telling me true now, but when I try to help people
I really don't like it when they throw me under the bus like that when I stick my neck out for someone
I don't like that man
But I want you to know I wasn't trying to do anything wrong this Sebastian. I was just trying to be myself
All right, how can I know you're telling it truly only gets really hard to tell
On the internet. Yeah, because yeah, that's because you don't really know me that well like psych and I we've known each other for a while
Yeah
Well, he's gone to know me to over the last few months and I haven't been on the stream for a while
But he knows me a little bit not much
Yeah, but even so I can tell you I'm not like that though and I don't just start any like fights or arguments or anything like that
I don't believe it
So I tell him like tell him what's going on with me
I was talking to a danger ranger, this guy a danger ranger.
I was just talking to him on Instagram in a friendly way.
I was not in a gait, nothing like hitting on him or anything.
So someone's posted like, I said I was going to gait date with him or something like that.
They're just trying to mock you. They're trying to embarrass you and mock you Patrick. That's what they're trying to do
Yeah, but it's like I hate how they like keep getting like
Nobody wants to talk to me look like
They horrible things and like, you know, she says that she says other people are hateful that rain
She comes on the panel and insults everyone and starts playing these dumb games and said no
It says no, but rude and vulgar things, you know, like what a what a hypocrite like why even have her on the panel
I would have told Stephanie take her off. What the heck?
I told you it's gonna go to a crap show if you let these idiots on your panel
If you let rain and GT and body on your panel is gonna go to a crap show and but she doesn't get it or
She likes it or she's letting it happen on purpose
Yeah, but Sebastian, what did I ever say one disrespectful word when I was talking on
He was saying anything respectful. I got the impression that you're playing dumb with me because I had your back
I stuck my neck out for you. And then you were so what are you saying? I'm balling. I was saying that you're not balling only
That's what I mean. I had the impression you're playing dumb then you're you're trying to
Well, I don't know to believe man. I just don't know to believe
Sebastian, I never said that you said that I was bald. I was saying that they were saying that stuff to me.
Yeah, and I was trying to tell you look he has air. I said look at that. He has hair on his head. He's got hair
Then you were saying that we're saying we're saying I'm both
Anyways, whether you're friends with them or not
Let me give you a warning Mason these these idiots these hypocrites and these liars they're gonna wrong you man
They don't care. They're not good people man. They got no standards. No values man. Watch out for them
Okay, they're gonna throw you under the bus and gonna back stab you the first chance again
Yeah, but Sebastian it's like and I we seem to get along with each other pretty good right site like you and I
Like I'm a pretty easy-going guy I can get along with anyone man, but I just don't like liars and hypocrites. That's one thing I don't like
I'm trying to explain to you Sebastian. I'm not trying to be that way though
All right, I'll give you the better for the doubt
That's what you say I can give you the better for the doubt
But Sebastian, you gotta give him some time man. Cyc will tell you he knows me like enough that I don't do stuff like that
Yeah, I don't get out of I don't get off line that much right side. You're very you'll barely
know
Well, that's like to he's seen me a few times. I'm a good guy, but I'm a very good guy
No, but yeah, you were the only one crazy Lee you and Mason had my back over there. I hope yeah
I was thinking my surprise
Sebastian don't think I didn't understand
Sebastian only thing I didn't understand is why y'all kept going back and forth with each other
Why couldn't I just end the conversation or make a better conversation to each other?
Well, yeah, I was surprised too because that's what she does Patrick, but but Mason that you should tell rain that we just told me
Why didn't she come on that panel right away? She insults people with vulgarities and obscenities
And nothing but rude talking men rude and disrespectful talking should be asking her that don't you think?
Yeah, I mean I agree with you. I'm just saying it went on too long though when y'all kept going back and forth that each other
I even told I warned that this to step me on the phone in private
I said watch out for these idiots there's a liar there liars and hypocrites and they're gonna turn your your stream into a
Crap show trust me on that but she doesn't listen. She doesn't take my advice. Let her learn the hard way, right?
No, Sebastian. I was on your side the whole time man. Even now. I mean, I'm still trying to still be on your side
You gotta let these guys I these people like to find out the hard way people like Stephanie
She wants to let people on her stream
But even after like you try to warn her about certain people they're gonna turn her stream into a crap show
She doesn't take it seriously. She's gonna find out the hard way
I mean
I hope that uh
I think that we gotta do you gotta be careful pageant you can't trust anyone you gotta be careful who you trust on these streams
On these chats
Anyways, how they did it like how she left your picture like on the screen like that for like a minute. I don't understand that
I don't know why she did that
She's looking for uh, she's looking at embarrass you man. I tried to make a show out of it
But that wasn't right. I found that was really uh, wasn't right on her part
I felt like that too
If it was me, I wouldn't have liked it then so I don't know why she did it like this
I'll talk to her on the phone about that next time I talked to Justin
Oh, yeah, I'll bring that up. Don't worry about don't worry about that
Who's the gay drummer? Mason is not gay. He's straight and he's a he's not bald. He has a full head of hair
Thank you. Thank you, Nick for saying that
Yes, like I was trying to tell you the whole time that I I mean I like women but I mean I don't mind being friends
They look guys. I just a whole life. I haven't never been gay
Okay, well not yet, but you want to try right with me, right?
It's like are you really want me to be gay though? I mean, yeah
No, I we need to be straight. I never just said it's experiment
Wait, what do you mean?
Experiment like just like
No
Sebastian it's hard to say if I like guys because I've been like with I mean
I've been into women like when I've been growing up and
Getting older stuff like that like looking for women to you know be with like the date and
I
And Jamie Cowboys, I want to ask you something Jamie Cowboys
Are you the one that tied me out when I was in that when I went down to the side chat and
Stephanie's stream there. You don't want to time me out
Yeah, no business doing that if you if you were the one doing that you have no business doing that whatsoever, man
I don't think Jamie
That's a woman. Yeah, yeah, no business doing that there lady
It's like hold on it's like hold on so you're gay your whole life, or did you just become gay like the person that's gay
I think they saw you I turned gay
What happens like
I'm banned from what
It's like wait what it's like. So when did you exactly become gay though like in your first kid became gay?
Yeah, but was it me though or what made you feel that way
World
It's like I'm I mean, I could it's like I've seen I could choose what I want
I don't have to do something just because somebody else tells me I have to I'm not saying anything wrong
I'm just saying no, no, I'm not telling you to do anything
I'm telling you just to do whatever you want. I'm saying what's like you're telling me no
It's like you're telling me to date you though. I never really did I mean there's always a first for everything
But it's like I don't want to make you so it's like I don't want to make you like feel like I'm saying something
That's against what you're saying, but it's hard to say like, you know
It's hard to say yes that I want to do sexually
So like I'm not gonna break your heart man, I'm still like your friend and stuff
But maybe in person it will give you nothing but shattered dreams
Shatter my dreams
Sebastian what is shattered dreams mean like what do you mean by that?
What is it as many things for that?
It's just as some people use that as a song and there's a few like lines from that one liners
Yeah, but what would it happen if I shatter somebody's dream is that a good thing or bad thing? It's a bad thing
but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but
It's like why don't you want to date you said you wanted to date I do but then you see you're like not interested now you are I
Never I don't know wait a Sebastian is that a cat
Yeah, that's my cat so you have a cat Sebastian
He just said he has a cat yeah, that's my cat
Wait, so are you gonna pet it though like Sebastian pet your cat?
I'm sitting down here. Oh
It's like you have a cat too. Oh, look at that. It's like she looks just like your cat. You see that
Like where's your cat right now?
He's not right. He's on the side right now. My cat looks exactly like Sykes cat
So yeah, it doesn't make tricks
Oh, yeah, same the same wait for on the front
It's like so I can go get your cat man so we can see it. I think the cat's outside
I really haven't put a lot of work into my website, psycheawakens.com, I mean, it's
pretty cool.
And so I would say go check that out and there's booklets available there too, but it will
have all my links to everything.
I've found a lot of social networks, you can find me other places and I think it's a cool
site though.
You can check it out.
It's a few links in the description.
Check out psych's work get 40% off your next liposuction surgery, by the way
It's like it's not even playing it's like the video is not even playing. It's suck
It's like that's me bet like watching yourself
You're a camera right now, right here right now, but you're not showing anything
Mason you smoke weed or do you do drugs
No tell me
You should I
Feel like I'm doing Sebastian Sebastian. Do you do that stuff? No, I
Don't do drugs. I don't drink I don't smoke I don't do anything man 100% sober
You don't smoke cigarettes. No, never
Oh
I've never really done sick. Uh, I never really done cigarettes much of my life, but I tried them this stuff before no
It's a disgusting habit. I don't like a smoking cigarettes terrible. It's disgusting. Yeah
Yeah, it is a disgusting habit. Yeah, I can't even date a girl that smokes
You know like the their breath stinks, you know, you come to you kiss a girl that the smokes man
She smells like cigarettes is terrible
Makes sense. Yeah, it's bad breath. It's bad. Yeah, man. It's in my breath. That's not like cigarettes. Would you still French kiss me?
I don't I don't think that would be that's not what I'm going for. I mean
If you had breath mints, though, it's like if you had breath mints, that'd be a different story. Okay. Well, what if I buy some breath mints?
Yeah
Okay, there's always a first it's like there's always a first for every day, right?
So that's gonna be great, okay
Yeah, I know there's not enough time in here. It's like it's like really like I feel like
Yeah, everyone's like just like what what is it's like? Why does it say don't trust them?
It's like he's full of something
Say, I don't know. Oh, sorry. Why don't I have that on the screen?
That's one of G teaser God he's a counts man
He's trying to cause problems with that. Yeah, that's one of his that's one of his accounts
It's either guy or JT or it's one of them
Yeah, that Patrick I never came on the panel once and you know the other time he promised he was gonna
He's gonna go on Jayce's panel the guy chickened out at the last minute. No surprise
guys a coward
Guys alive
Sebastian you never kissed a girl who is kidding now that guy's lying that guy's a piece of crap
I had a bunch of girlfriends in my life man
dozens of them
And this really beautiful Vietnamese girlfriend about 10 years ago 15 years ago
Yeah, she was Vietnamese Patrick she was Vietnamese my girlfriend
She was beautiful, man. She was something she was exotic
That Patrick New York guys are coward he never goes on any panel
He just hides in the side chat and says dumb things. He's a total coward
Sebastian hit Sebastian. What is that Sebastian? What do you mean? It's a total coward. He's an idiot
I mean, he's jealous of people like me. He's just a successful people like me and maybe you were
Psych, you know, he's just a good good people that got the courage to go on the panel
Yeah, but it's like, you know me. I don't really you know, I don't really feel jealous about anybody else's stuff like that
that Patrick guys Joe so he's Joe's everyone that goes on a panel especially intelligent people like me
Why don't you come on the panel then Patrick New York
Let's see what it looks like Sebastian show it just passed by there she is
There she is you see her. It's coming in the room now
Sebastian DC a Sykes cat wait Sykes were sure cat
Yeah, Sebastian I can see man
That's her man. That's her. Oh, yeah, they look the same. I say
The best your cat looks the same. Yeah, look look at the white on the paws and in the neck
There's Lola Lola even say hi to
She's RBF
Okay
What's going on tonight? How's everybody in chat again? Yeah, I don't know like
Elsewhere, you know like some of the hopefully I didn't say too many bad too many bad things in that
Have videos like sometimes when people talk like this they
So I I
Don't think Sebastian plays video games anymore like we do
You don't think he plays video games anymore, but yeah, yeah, yes
Yes, best told me doesn't play video games anymore site
Sebastian's that true
Yeah, I'm not into video games anymore. You have a VR headset
No, I don't got that now
Can afford a man I got bigger fish to fry I got more important things to buy right now to pay for
So best you got it. You got to work towards harder stuff right or better stuff like that mean more see
What do you want to
So that's what do you want to buy man when you get money and stuff like that when you trying to aim for like stuff for all
They suffer on the house
No, I'm just trying to pay off my debts man
And I'm just trying to survive man just paying the regular bills every month ends up cost me a fortune
True. Yeah, I've been 1100 bucks a month just for rent electricity internet
You have to pay all that and that takes up a lot of your money though
Yeah, then I know we've got a then I got to pay like for you like you know monthly expenses
I'm always on a tight budget. I'm always tight man. I'm always poor
Well, I feel like I am too a little bit, but I mean it's like I'm luckily have a roof over my head and like
It does everything else is expensive, and especially even just like oh, yeah, that's what matters patch
You got a you got in your apartment. You got your apartment. You're like, you're seeing that baby. It's fine
I mean, I paid my electricity in the water my my heating with the gas bill that
Cable they all so it's a good you never been
You never been homeless before Sebastian. No after I was always at an apartment. I'm happy about that man
I don't take that for granted. You know an apartment's the most important thing you can have
Yeah, you don't want to be on the street you need your own bathroom
You're on washroom and your own bed. I need your privacy that I value. Yeah, I
Valley my privacy
Like that's obviously that's what you like about having your own place your own home
Yeah, well, I like having my own a shower my own bathtub my own wash no one else uses it
And like a I don't need to live with anyone. That's like dirty or not clean
Again, I can have a loan. I don't need to worry about I got my privacy
That's a good thing Sebastian. Yeah
Oh, yeah, I still I still rather have that like I may be broke but darn at least I got that I paid out
I paid my electricity internet
No rent I paid everything I had to pay I always paid my bills
Did you pay for food though or anything like that? I'm always tied on food, man
I'm always tight sometimes he wants every two days many we can get you know like it ain't easy
Yeah, but you can get whatever food that you can afford though or you know by you know
Sometimes you report you got to eat peanut butter out of the jar man with a spoon like you got to eat once every two days
You got to drink water for supper sometimes if you're really poor that's how bad it is
But oh well, and there's there's worse right at least I'm not on the street
Yeah, but Sebastian, I've had to do that before myself and I've been there's times where I actually had to eat peanut butter out of a
I need peanut butter out of a jar and stuff like that. I've done that before with this like spoon and stuff like that
Yeah, that's what I did yesterday. I had peanut butter for supper yesterday
Did you eat it on a spoon though Sebastian? You said it on a spoon. Yeah, I eat peanut butter out of the jar with a spoon
That's what I'm saying. Yeah. Yeah, these are so bad ever since I had to file for file for bankruptcy for my bad for my
Liposuction surgery company. I haven't been poor ever since
Been going downhill ever since the bankruptcy
Well, what I mean at least yeah, let me say at least you got things still going for you though, right?
So this there's nothing you could like
There's nothing you could complain about right? No, I'm not on the street. I got my cat. I got my apartment my privacy
Those are good things. I appreciate that. No, I live in gratitude. I try to live in gratitude
Yeah
You know some people in countries. They got to walk like two days just to get water
You know got nothing to eat nothing to drink. You know, I've got a roof over their heads
Yeah
Sebastian you're right. I mean like I heard about stuff like that happening. Yeah
People take that for granted having your own apartment having your privacy your own your own shower your own bathtub your own toilet people take that for granted
Wait, what do you wait? Hold on?
Sebastian, what do you mean people take it for granted though? Like what makes some people granted?
Well, some people they think they got it harder than they do like I appreciate everything you gotta appreciate what you got in life
Yeah
We're very fortunate in America
I can see when you're on when you're on the street, you don't got your privacy
You don't got a your own toilet your own washroom. You know, I can go to the wash many time
I want I can use a shower. I can use the sink. I can drink water like it's still not bad compared to people that are on the street
So how'd you never become homeless before Sebastian like I
Always paid my rent man. I always worked before I always paid my rent
I mean, you know, I was in I was in between jobs, man
I always managed to pay my rent. That's the important thing pay your rent once I what a few times
I was like one month behind but I always caught up
I always caught up on the second month and I pay two months rent you only you got to pay your your rent
That's the most important thing in life
Yeah, that's only if you could do it though Sebastian there's a difference if you can't
Well, if you can't do it
I mean you got to try to talk to your owner, but but sometimes your owners are the owners they own a they're not patient
They're gonna kick you out if you don't pay so you got to find a way you got a
You're saying some people get eviction some people get eviction like notices or something like that, right?
Oh, yeah, I have some people get evicted man. They don't pay their rent. You got to pay your rent
That's a top priority. You got to pay your rent before you buy food before you buy food
You got to literally pay your rent in full
And that's really right is something
Like sometimes like I pay my rent, I got nothing left, but I say at least I paid the rent because the owner doesn't care
They know it says where's the rent money?
They don't care if you're starving the owner just wants their rent money
So you got to pay him the rent money and then you can worry about food later
Like you can always go to food banks or whatever. Maybe your friend can he can help you out
Give you some bread or whatever some peanut butter, you know, but you gotta you gotta pay your rent
Sebastian but not everybody has it that way though. That's why there's people in the world that are less fortunate
Oh, I know man, but that's when you got to tell your owner you got to tell your owner give me a few weeks or get
Give him a month like me. I was like an example
I was one month behind and I paid off two thousand bucks in one month man. I paid it off and I promise you
It's just the or says alright. I'm gonna let you get that take another month
But at the end of the month you got to pay the two months rent or or you're out
I said, don't worry. I give you my word and I gave it to him
And I kept my word and they like that when I went on I see you keep your word. They they like it
They like it. No, they appreciate it
Yeah, but if you don't see if you don't keep your word then they're gonna kick you out
Then they're gonna take you to the rental board and you'll lose your apartment
It only take a few weeks to evict someone when you were the way when it's for non payment of rent you get evicted right away
Trust me. You don't want to mess with it
Sebastian I try to stay away from like, you know, making mistakes like
Well, you gotta put the right money ahead of everything man
I see that
I can't buy food like I had to put everything aside and just focus on the red money clear the red money then the rest it's it's secondary
I can worry about the rest after I pay the rent
So wait what wait hold on Sebastian. What comes secondary though?
Secondary secondary be like your food and your electricity and your internet, but no matter what you gotta pay the rent
I
You mean it always comes first, right? Yeah, the rent always comes first
Cuz even like whether the electricity in the internet you can maybe make it like a an agreement
You can call the customer service to tell them give me another month or two
But but the red men they're not gonna wait for long if you're more than like two three weeks behind
They're gonna take you the rental board. You'll be a victim. You can't mess with that. You gotta pay your rent
I've learned it. I've learned it, you know live like, you know within my means though special like what I happen stuff
Yeah, well, that's what I do. I live within my means man like like I eat a can of soup for supper or some peanut butter
Like I drink water man. I can't even buy a juice in the store
What can I say like when you're poor you're poor man, but you got to deal with it. You got to make the best of it
You got to tighten your belt
You know you got to you got to you got to tighten your belt and just deal with it
And maybe later on in a few months you'll you'll get some money
But when you're poor you just got to do it is depressing. It is depressing, but there's worse. There's worse
But when you pay the rent, you don't need to worry like you can sleep at night knowing that you're not gonna get evicted
You know like that's that's that's peace of mind
No, but uh, no, but Sebastian there's worse things that happen when he don't you know, like like say you're homeless, right?
Anything can happen to you like actually out on the street stuff like that. I know I've seen so many people on the street
I've seen people lose their apartments because they didn't pay their rent
Yeah, but there's so much weird things that happen out there in the real world like, you know bad things I
Mean I'm talking about like when you're uh
Tell me when you're not able to pay for certain things and you get like homeless or something else
Like once I was in apartment. I was talking to this guy. He told me this guy told me he was like he lost everything
He had like he lost his red money in the machines
I said you should gotta at least pay the rent and whatever you got left then you can play the machines
But don't mess around don't mess around the rent money
You don't want to lose your apartment because it's so hard to get an apartment these days
Once you lose your apartment you're on the street for a long time if you can ever get an apartment ever again
It's almost impossible these days to get an apartment if you don't got a perfect credit
You don't got a job and a perfect credit not gonna find an apartment
Yeah, but there's always ways around that though Sebastian
Really man, if you don't get anyone to like sign for you with you
If you don't get a friend or a failing member that can sign for you if you have bad credit that you get you're out of luck
You're not gonna find apartment against down the street or at best
You're gonna be able to rent a room in someone's apartment, but you'll never have your own apartment. That's what I mean
I got my own apartment. I'm happy now
I've been having this apartment out for a year and a half man before I had to rent a room before with other people in Mason
It's not fun living with other people, especially if they're not cleaning the washroom and stuff,
and they make noise at night, or whatever in the morning they make noise when they get up.
It ain't fun to live with other people.
Wait Sebastian, what do you mean? They make noise when they get up like what kind of noise is did they make like when they
Oh, like they like they pulled the chair
Did they slam doors hit doors hard and they make noise enough to wake you up like see you're trying to sleep in like a six o'clock
Or seven o'clock in the morning or whatever they like when you're looking at
Turn the lights on sometimes when you're trying to still sleep in your bed, you don't want to light on because
You're trying to sleep it's no I'm not telling you like that like when you're running a room
I'm when you're running a room in an apartment you got your own room
It's not the light that bothers you you can hear the noise through the wall
I mean through the door like a like I'm sleeping my room with the door closed
I'm everyone has their own room where I was renting a room before like two years ago
And this guy goes in the washroom and hits the door real hard and makes a bunch of noise
It pulls back the chairs like it's a wooden chair on a wooden floor
So it's gonna screech on the floor like this guy makes so much noise
He wakes me up in the morning
I said can't you be more careful in the morning man, and there's other people sleeping in the apartment
I thought so I told myself there's other people I told there's other people sleeping in the apartment
You idiot and he that guy that guy's on drugs
You know that guy's happy his brains are fried on drugs most of the time like he doesn't even realize what he's doing
Or he doesn't care. He's got no consideration
But anyways, my point is it's not fun to live with other people when you got your own privacy
You don't need to deal with that crap
No, Sebastian, I know what that's like man
I've been through group home and stuff like that where you have to live with other people that you don't even know
You don't even want to live with or you never lived with before in your life
Exactly, that's what happened to me that where I was at my last apartment
It was a five bedroom apartment gave there was four different rooms and we were four guys
We were three guys running a we were three guys living in the same apartment
We each had our own room, but Darnie you got to share the bathroom and you got to share the kitchen other people when people aren't clean
It's always arguments and it's problems man
It sucks like that like I dealt with it for a year and eight months
And sometimes you almost got into a fight and into a fight in the kitchen
Oh cuz arguing about so I said why don't you guys wash your hands when you go to the washer and you guys take a number two
You don't even wash your hands
Yeah, that's disgusting
You're gonna touch everything the door handles and the faucets the tap water fuss and you're gonna touch the fridge
So Sebastian, how do you know about that though? Like, how would you know if they don't wash?
I know I know why because because it's when it's quiet, you don't hear anything
You know they go in the washroom and you don't hear any like it when they flush the toilet
You don't even hear the sink like they don't use the sink
They just open the door and they come out of the washroom. I know the guy didn't wash his hands
Tell the guy look man wash your hands. I'm touching the other door handles like you every time I don't even use the door handles
I gotta like open it with my foot like from the door of my foot and I gotta use a paper phone to touch the handles
I don't like those guys grossed me out and they disgust me because I was the only guy that washed my hands with soap
You know because I'm a clean guy, but they weren't
And these guys like I told you guys not wash your hands. You're living with other people
That's the least of things of consideration
It shows you gotta show further people and wash your hands for crying out loud man
Even a kid like you gotta talk to him like they're a kid. You gotta tell him wash your hands
And you gotta tell us to adults to wash your hands when they think of dump, you know, you believe that
Yeah, but yeah, I'm gonna try to laugh babe. I'm just saying
Yeah, it's kind of ridiculous Sebastian because like it's not hard to do something like that
You just put your hands over the water and you soap and that's it
Oh, yeah
Because they weren't making fun of me because I took a little bit longer in the washroom
Because I took longer in the showers and the washing like when I think number two
I wash my hands and I got to wash the faucets and I got to wipe down the sea
Because of them because they gross me out and they say oh you take a long time
No, I don't take a long time because I take the time wash my hands
Plus I got to wash the stuff because are you idiots that they're not clean
Hell yeah, plus I take a lot of time to wash them because that's another story me. I mean, I got OCD and I take a long time in the shower
Okay
I love myself and I watch myself like eight times. I think a long time. I think a long shower like 30 minutes or 40 minutes
Wait, so I mean a Sebastian. Why do you take so much longer showers though?
Why can't you just take like a short shower? I take short showers sometimes but usually I take a long shower
If I really want to go fast and I think just a 15 minute shower
But if I take my time, I think at least 30 minutes
But the longer you take your shower though the more it just um like it like say you live with other guys
They got to use a shower too though, right?
Well, yeah, but that's another thing. I take the time don't worry. I got consideration for them
I take the time to take a shower. I asked them do you need to wash them? I saw it and they say no go ahead
All right, I think I take the shower take my time
I make sure that they've already used it so I don't empty the hot water tank and there's no hot water left for them
I always take a shower and they don't need to wash them like I take it a certain time like when they're not there
They're there. They don't need to use it. I always ask I said, do you need the wash or I plan taking a shower?
It's gonna take 30 minutes. You need to take a piss hurry up
I could go take a piss before I take a shower, you know stuff like that like a show consideration
I think about them, you know, yeah, but yeah, but there's it's hard when you do that one
You only have one restroom and it's not to like a restroom is like in the same
Place you live in and it's easy. It's easy enough. Trust me when there's only three people in the apartment
You just see it's not hard you go in the washroom when you need like you ask him if they need to use a washroom
You need to take a shower
That's fine. Like sometimes they're the guys I said no go ahead go before me
I said go go in the washroom do your stuff take your shower before me because I know I'm gonna take longer than you
Like I know I'm gonna take longer than just 15 minutes like you yeah, I'm gonna take 30 to 40 minutes
So go ahead and take your shower for me then I'll take a shower after because I know I think
Yeah, but you got to make sure they don't use up all the hot water like you're explaining before
Well, why sometimes I had to take cold showers, but I didn't even complain about that
I didn't even complain about it. You know, like I don't listen
Yeah, I just asked for them to wash their hands when they take a dump. That's the only thing I asked for
Yeah, I mean I got OCD man and and people gross me out man
I got to watch that the faucets like a like a few times and like three four times everything
I do like I take a shower
I lather I I soap up and I lather for like six to eight times like I think that's why I take one showers man
Because I got a bit of OCD. Yeah, especially in the shower
What happened to site though, so that's where they go. No, he does that sometimes he gets off the panel
He's just letting us talk. He's doing other stuff
Oh, so it's just us right now Sebastian you and I does that he does that Mason sometimes. Oh
Yeah
Sebastian who's that Mary Hopkins? I don't know. Oh
She's a regular she has a wrench. She's a regular
If she's got a wrench that means she's a regular do you see her though Sebastian see her picture. Yeah, I see her
What do you think about her? Is she cool? She's not bad looking
Would you date her though?
Of course I dated her man
You would date her right?
Yeah, Mary Mary Hopkins. How's it going? How's it? How's it?
Now she's beautiful just fine. She's good looking
Hey, hey, um, hey, Sebastian, can you show me what you look like on camera? I showed you me earlier
No, I never do that man. I never go on camera
Show me one
Why don't you like to show yourself though, Sebastian?
For privacy purposes and the other thing I don't want to turn on the women. It might make them too excited. You know
I'm not looking to do that
You never do it at all like never want to get on camera or never on screen. Well, I've shown pictures of myself a few times
I've actually shown pictures of myself a few times, but I don't go on camera. No
You know, I'm afraid camera at all. No, I'm afraid for a friend like I don't want to excite the women and it's for privacy purposes
You know, the women might get too aroused and you know, they might get too excited
Yeah
But like but yeah, but Sebastian site goes on camera and I do her once in a while
Oh, but I don't man. I tell you you can't be too careful. It can never be
What I mean is you gotta know when to hold them and you got you gotta know when to fold them you see what I mean
You gotta know when to hold them and you got no one to what you gotta know when to hold them and you got no one to fold them I
Don't understand that
Gotta read between the lines my friend
Read between the lines. Oh, yeah, you got to read between the lines
So Sebastian hold on man like so you're saying you don't have a girlfriend man, but you like women
Of course, man. I've loved women my entire life. I had a girlfriend before it's just now man
I've it's hard to find a girlfriend. You're a good girlfriend. That's really hard to find Mason
Yeah
It's not easy out. There's no women here in my neighborhood right now. You know, like I don't even go out much
Oh, I'm not even trying to find a girlfriend right now. Like I got other problems. I'm depressed and I'm working on
I'm trying to better myself here. I'm not even like ready to get married. So I stay on my own
I just live with my cat for now. It's enough
It's not responsibility man, I just live with my cat you see there's only your cat that you live with
Yeah
Just nobody else
Sebastian nobody else like just me and her just me and my cat
Well, I live with three people if you counted me myself and I that's three people
Yeah
So you have a job Sebastian
Yeah, I just lost my job. I had to have a bankruptcy. I mean I had to fall for bankruptcy. I had a liposuction surgery
company business going for about
About a few months ago I had to fall for bankruptcy
Why'd you have to fall for bankruptcy? What happened many problems some of their clients some of our fat clients weren't paying their
Their bills some of our fat customers we gave them this we gave them the surgery when came time to pay their bills
They they simply didn't pay their bills. Yeah
Why they got off like cheap
Yeah, but that's the thing that's those some of the risks when you go in business
You can't do anything about that Mason. That's part of the deal. I mean it's part of the part of the game
Those are the risks those are the risks involved of having your own business
Yeah
I retire from that though. I retire from the corporate world. I used to be the executive director of strategy and operations and marketing for a few
Few high-end liposuction surgery clinics across the USA and again in the Atlantic and northeastern part of the country
But I don't do that anymore
I just live my own now now my full-time job Mason, you know my full-time job
It's to take care of my cat. I'm a full-time caretaker my cat. That's my job now
So bad shit, so how do you make it though? That's all you do. Oh
I tell you
Well, how do you make it now? What do you do? I?
Just live off of social security, man. Oh, yeah
You know what SSI is right? Yeah, I know that
That's what I love off of man. Yeah, nothing wrong with that man. If you think that's all you got man
At least you got something right?
Yeah, it's better than nothing man, of course man, it pays the bills if it pays the bills it pays the rent
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Yeah, there's nothing wrong with that man
At least if you're not like you're not hurting anyone
You're not like a criminal like it. There's no shame about that man
If you if you got any beyond that then this is no no one to judge you
No, but Sebastian if I get um
If I could work a job I would though, but I don't have a job though right now
Yeah, speaking of that and I actually look for a job, and you know in the summertime I was looking for a job
Yeah, I was looking I want to do a bunch of things. I was gonna work in maybe a
In a warehouse or maybe even like as a dishwasher like I was looking for anything
I was looking for a full-time job
But I couldn't even find them because there's no jobs around here in my city and everything's full and there's too many people
That apply for jobs. There's no positions available
Why why is it so hard to find a job nowadays bet everybody else has one and there's
No, because there's too many people especially in the big cities
There's like one job for a hundred people same thing with apartments
That's why you see so many people on the street or so many people homeless
Because there's just not enough apartments and they always take the best person like the person that has a job
That's a good credit. You know like if you have a bad credit
You don't got a job or any references forget it. You're not gonna find anything you won't find an apartment
You won't even find a job
So what can you do though Sebastian like where that happens like what's the best thing to do you got to get lucky man
You got a something someone has to give you a chance
Someone has to give you a break it give you a job give you a chance give you an apartment
If you don't get lucky you might be on the street for a long time
I mean you might be running a rumor you're not gonna have your own place for a long time if you're out of luck
No, you gotta get lucky
No Sebastian, I know what it's like to be like homeless. I've been homeless before man
Yeah
Oh, it's not easy
He said you've never been homeless before though. Yeah, yeah, that's the one thing like I've lost jobs
I quit jobs. I lost jobs, but I've never been homeless because I always pay my rent
Like I always held an apartment
I kept an apartment and I always did sideline work and I I was always able to survive Mason like somehow I was always
Able to find a way to pay the rent money and survive and sometimes I had to rent rooms
Living with people but that's not fun. That's why it's better to have your own apartment
The only thing you're doing is like
Sebastian, I know what it's like man to be like with the you know other people that you had to live with especially when they're not even from your
Same family there's people like from other walks of life
And they come from anywhere and they live with you and stuff like that
I thought the most part like we got along when I was living in an apartment with three other people like about a year and a half ago
We respect each other
Sebastian that's called a group poll. No, it's not a group all because it was an apartment us as we were just renting an apartment
It's the owner. He we were paying the rent of the owner, but we're sharing the apartment
It's we got three different rooms, but we had our own separate rooms in the apartment
Anyways, and we respect each other's privacy
But what I didn't like is some of the guys they weren't clean and they were make too much noise
And that that was hard to put up with I had to be very patient for a long time. I think it is I stay paid
Wait Sebastian, how's it not a group home though if there's other guys that you don't even know
I thought that's called a group home though. Well, it depends what you call it
Because it's not in the house. That's what I mean. It's an apartment in an apartment building
It's not a group home because you're you're paying the rent to the owner and the owners are the owner of the building an apartment building
You see what I mean an apartment building
Wait, I don't completely understand Sebastian like help me understand like I don't know man
You know you guys call in the USA here in Canada you're living in it in an apartment
You're paying rent to an apartment to a to a building owner to a building owner, man
It's an apartment building, you know, it's an apartment building in a group home and you're living in an apartment in the apartment
There's there's three or four rooms in a five-bedroom apartment and you're sharing the apartment with other people
But yeah, everyone has their own room. So it's not a group home. You know what I mean? It's an apartment
You're living in an apartment. You're just sharing the apartment with other people
Yeah, but I mean I just know about group pump because I've been in that before but I don't think I've ever been in a
Apartment with people like that you tell them about people that you don't even know right or you never
Grew up with or never seen in your life or you're just trying to get the
Oh, yeah, you know, I remember this one that actually once I lived in a house in 2004
I guess you call it room. I lived outside the city at that time
I lived in the suburbs mason and it was this house and we were eight people living in one house
but it was a huge house like the guy had the guy had like six rooms upstairs and
Four rooms in the basement. I think like it was a huge house and this guy was renting us each room for two
250 bucks back then 2004 and that's a long time. That's like 19 years ago
Like it was it was really cheap back then that was a good deal 250 for running a room there
Although the cost of life was cheaper back then I live with people like that. I know it's like
So that's actually from like what year though that was 2004 I just told you 2004
19 years ago
21 years ago. I mean yeah, 21 years ago 2004. That's 21 years ago. Yeah, that's a long time ago man
That's over two decades ago
So so so I'm guessing that you were like only like the teenager when you weren't there
I was I was in 2024 I was 23 because I'm 44 now 44 and a half. I was 23 in 2004
23 and a half in 2004
Anyways, I ran in the room with people in the house, but yeah
Yeah, it was fun sometimes like we got along some of the guys who got along we joked around
We went down the kitchen and we joked around and we ate together
We we hung around with each other in the kitchen. It was fun. It was an adventure
She had a special he told me that you got into some kind of fights or something like that
No, no, I'm talking about recently after I'm the thing about 2004 is when I rented a room in a house with people
But in recently like a year and a half ago. I was running a like in 2023
I was running a 2023 in the first half of 2024 is running a I was running a room in an apartment
And we're three people sharing the apartment
That's what I we always had fights in the kitchen because this one case is two of the guys one guy was on drugs
The other guy will he was just not clean
He didn't find it important to wash his hands when he took a dump
We had we literally had arguments because of that in the kitchen and we were gonna fight because of that
I said wash your hands you you disgusting piece of crap. I don't want to touch your crap man
You're gonna wash your hands when you go in that wash you're gonna bring soap with you
And you're gonna wipe yourself properly and you're gonna wash your hands man. I'm sick of this crap man
I told my sick of this nonsense. What are you? I said you're 40 years old man. I said grow up
wash your hands that's what I told the guy yeah yeah but Sebastian like not
everybody does the right things you know people are gonna do whatever they
want they don't care what like happens
Actually that guy wasn't for I think it was 38. It was about a few years younger than me
But anyways, yeah, he didn't understand. Well, he didn't even find it important like him to him
What's important smoking cigarettes and and talking a lot on the phone in the apartment?
I know and then washing his hands. That's not a priority for him
I told him you're gonna make it a priority man
Because you know why he was giving me crap or not for not like wiping the kitchen counters
Like there's a few drops of water from when I go in the sink and when I was washing it like dishes in the sink
I'm in the kitchen when I was cooking stuff and I said you're gonna complain about a few drops of water
You can't even wash your hands on them wash
you're disgusting piece of crap I told I said what I said I'll start washing the kitchen counter when you
Start washing your hands when you go in the washroom. I told him. What do you think of that? That's what I told him
Wait, I don't know wait what happened now, especially I heard what you said, but I didn't get the whole story
I think that guy was giving me a hard time because when I used to wash dishes or stuff
I used to like a go and say like I was gonna cook myself a soup in the kitchen and I was washed my hands
Like there's a few drops of water around the around the the sink, you know the kitchen sink
You know around the kitchen sink
There's a few drops of water and he says I want you to wipe the the thing there. Yeah, I wipe it
But I said you when you go in the washroom, you don't even wash your hands with soap
You're disgusting piece of crap. His name was Patrick. Actually, there's many Patrick's and I told him
I said you gotta wash your hands when you go in that washroom. I said, I want you to bring soap
I say how come you don't bring soap with you when you go in the in the washroom
I bring soap with me every time because that's how we did we used to bring our own
Like toilet paper our own soap and our own stuff like in the washroom when we take a shower and everything
You know, like everyone has their own toilet their own toilet paper their own soap their own
Conditioners their own stuff, you know, like, you know, sure anyone's told me like we are you got to bring in your own stuff when you're
Everyone lives on by themselves in their own rooms, you know, we close our doors
We just we stay in the kitchen sometimes when we talk. That's the only time we see each other
There's one we're in the kitchen or in the hallway together, you know
yeah
So it's not fun living with people Mason and any fun living with people I can tell you
I much prefer my my my privacy in my own apartment. I don't need to deal with that stuff. There's no more arguments, you know
Yeah, but Sebastian hold on man
I'm saying like there's ways you can actually um
There's actually ways you can actually get that you know to be better for you if you just give them advice
Or they're just not gonna take your advice. Oh, I first I tried trust me believe me man
I talked to him nicely at first, but they didn't get it and then they said I was exaggerating
I said exaggerating. Are you kidding me? You you don't wash your hands and you got literally crap on your hands
You're gonna touch the doors and you expect me to touch the same door handle as you
You expect me to not find that gross and disgusting but then you're gonna complain about about
Drops of water on the sink on around the kitchen sink a few drops of water around the kitchen sink that bothers you
But the fact that what I'm not supposed to be bothered by you now washing your hands in the washroom
I said you kidding me. I said wash your hands. You're disgusting. You're disgusting jerk, man
I said what the heck's wrong with you, man? Even a kid knows to wash their hands even a kid. No, that's just good manners
You know, it's a force of habit when you go in the washroom don't you wash your hands?
Especially when you're living with other people. That's the least of things, you know, yeah
Anyways, man, it's that's it
That's to tell you Mason. I'm happy. I don't live with other people anymore
I don't I don't particularly enjoy living with people that people are disgusting and they're not clean
Sebastian, so have you ever lived with their mom before I moved out when I was 18
I moved out of my mom's house when I was 18, man. I had my first full-time job
Man, I worked when I was 14, but I my first I quit high I quit high school
I had my first full-time job at 18
I moved out man never been never went back since man. I've been on my own since 18 since age 18
Did you ever did you ever actually move back in with your mom ever though in your life, though?
You just hear what I told you man. I just told you I answered you
I said I ever since age eight. I said since the age 18. I never went back man
I moved out and I've been on my own ever since since age 18 man since 1999
I got no Sebastian. I got that but I'm just saying like did you ever have a chance to actually go back to your mom?
Do like our eggs move back in? No, no, no Mason. No, I don't want to go back
I would never go back to living my family. No, no, man. I'm not like that. I need to be alone. I need my privacy
I don't like living with my family, man. I like being alone. I'm a loner like that in life
You know, like I live with my girlfriend or live with a wife or a friend, but I'm not gonna live with my family
No, no, none of that crap, you know
Sebastian but what's wrong with family families supposed to be good to you now
Well, you got to get along with your family and you guys you don't have enough in common ain't gonna work man
Plus it's uncomfortable man. You know when you you're an adult man. You're living with your family. It's it's weird man
I can't do it. I could not live with my family man
I need my my space with my price like when you're an adult man
You got to move out make a man yourself and that's what I did man
I got out when I was 18 and ever since then been alone been on my own
are you happy though? Like Sebastian, are you happy like living on your own though?
No, I had better days and I had better days, but I am happy, yeah?
I had better days though.
Yeah, I wasn't always poor, man. I wasn't always tight on money.
I once had a nice job and nice girlfriend and everything, but now those days are gone.
But oh well, I got a nice cat now. I got a nice cat and I got a nice apartment, so I'm not gonna complain, right?
so bashing you can't complain if you got things still going for you though like
As long as you still have something going for you then things should be like the way there's I mean not exactly the way it's supposed to be
But there's still the way they are supposed to be what about you are you happy right now?
Hey, what do you say you living in a group home right now? Are you living on your own?
No, I wasn't living in a group home before though, but not anymore
What you got now if you got to get an apartment you're not on the street, hopefully
No, Sebastian. I was on the streets for a while, but then I found a group home
And I lived in a group home for like a while, but I moved away from that. Yeah, well, what do you got now?
That's what I'm asking. What do you got now?
Wait, what do you mean what I got now like I don't understand. What do you got now?
Where do you live now? You got your own apartment? Where do you live right now? I?
Live like an apartment. Yeah, you got your own apartment right now for yourself
Yeah, that's good. That's what I got. I got my own party see look
That's my apartment see that that's my apartment. That's my room here. I got two rooms right now. I'm on my room here
So I keep the door wide open
Yeah, but Sebastian, how is it though? Like what is it? What is it like to be there?
Why you got your privacy man? Even even actually I'm talking too loud right now because I don't want to wake people up
They're living upstairs, but it's fun to have your own privacy
Way Sebastian there's living up something by other people so you can't talk low
No, because I live in an apartment building and then and then it's wooden floors
You know and everything in like you can hear the noise through the walls man. It's not made out of cement
It's it's made out of wood. It's made out of wooden and
You see a sheet rock, you know the walls are thin the walls are thin
So if you talk too loud, you're gonna wake up people if they're sleeping, you know
Because you can hear through the the walls and through the ceiling and through the floor
Sebastian what he got to do like to actually make things like you know better though
I mean like not to be like, you know the way you're saying
Why you ask me that then you should be asking yourself that
I'm just saying I can't figure out how to fix that
Don't worry about that don't worry about me man. I'm surviving. I'm not complaining. I'm happy. It's like I said there's people on the streets
I got my apartment. I'm not complaining
It does get lonely though it does get lonely but don't don't get me wrong not having a girlfriend for like 15 years
Man, that's gonna make you very lonely and depressed, but they could be worse
Sebastian I'm just saying things are not the way they're really all the way. I mean you can't complain. I couldn't understand that
But I'm saying like there's no way to really make things like you know, like go in your favor
If you have no way to get things going in your favor
Yeah, but now I take it one day at a time
If I'm battling depression, I'm battling other stuff man like other mental problems like anxiety and depression
And right now I actually got a sciatic nerve man
I got a terrible nerve pain in my back my lower back and my my hip there man. It's I
Got other problems right now. So I always oh well, it could be worse
Anyway, I got an apartment. I'm not complaining. I'm not on the street. I can't complain. I
Got my apartment. I paid the rent
Sebastian so you're okay like right now with the way things are going though for you
At least she likes at least you had a place to be and stuff like that
Yeah, exactly exactly Mason
But I'm saying can't you find ways to work around that though?
Like if you can't find any other way to get things going for you though
Because you said you don't have a job so how else are you gonna find a way to do things?
My second I didn't hear you what
How else are you gonna be able to find a way to do things if you don't have a job
You got to be able to find a way to work around like those kind of things
Well, believe me man. I ever since like the month that like may have ever since I thought for bankruptcy man
I've been looking for a job and I couldn't find one. It's it's really hard to find a job in this big city
There's just nothing here right now, man. Believe right now. There's nothing in the big city for me right now
I can't even be a dishwasher. There's nothing. There's no work available
I take a job I take a job as a dishwasher in a restaurant if I could I take anything right now, but almost anything. There's nothing
Sebastian so there's nothing you could do like to get things going like the way that I mean like you
I get that like I said before I get that have an apartment or place to live is the one step to being happy
But it's not gonna fulfill your whole like
It's not gonna fill fill like everything you still need to happen in your life like the stuff
We're still really supposed to go through in your life
Oh
Well, I just uh, well, I take it one day at a time
Again really if I really wanted everything if I had everything I'd have a little bit more money
And I have like a girlfriend or a wife, but I don't got that so oh well you can't have everything, right?
You can't have
No, Sebastian, I'm not saying you're supposed to have everything and I'm not saying it's that's the way supposed to be like what I'm saying
Being at home. That's not gonna get things like really accomplished unless you find a way to get things more accomplished like for yourself
Look at that guy that that guy in the side chat that Patrick New York guy
He's desperate for a discount on liposuction screws. I ain't gonna give it to him
He's got the wrong attitude. He ain't gonna bring that trash into my house
He ain't gonna get the discount. You see that Mason?
What are you talking about that guy in the side chat that guy Patrick New York in the side chat
He's not gonna get anything from me. He's not even gonna get 20% he's not gonna get anything
Sebastian give yourself half off like both suck just surgery to suck the stupid out of your head
Yeah, he's just joking around. He's trying to give me a hard time
But that that coward that guy's never been on the panel once because he's afraid at least you you went on the panel in Mason
You're able to talk on the panel. So you I get I got more respect for you cuz you're not a coward like him, you know
No, but no, no
No, but Sebastian you got a true point there. Yeah, of course. He's a coward
He's been hiding in the side chat for months. I've never seen that guy go on the panel once
He's too afraid anything say and then he thinks I'm gonna give him like a discount on liposuction surgery ain't gonna happen
Sebastian you're not gonna make it easy for him like right he's gonna need to stay fat or he's gonna need to look at other clinics
Well, he's not gonna get any of the 40% discounts for the clinics. I'm working for that for sure
Yeah
Sebastian I don't know what to tell you bet about that and I never seen that Jamie Cowboys person come on the panel either
Wait so hold on Sebastian what it's like gonna come back to or is he just gonna be gone?
You know, he might be gone for the night. Sometimes I seen him do that
He does he does his offer sleeps and he's gone for hours and then he wakes up and he closes down the stream sometimes it turns it off
You mean he might have fell asleep or something like that or what?
Well, yeah, he's probably gone and don't don't uh, don't put any pornography now, but he's probably gone man
I think he's gone. I think he fell asleep
He's been gone for a long time
What do you mean don't put any pornography or something like that? Why would you say such fuck as other people do that?
You know, they've done it sometimes
Some people do what have they done though Sebastian. I've seen some people like I've seen some people when they're on a panel
And the person like the host they're gone
They put some pornography thing and then the then the channel gets like shut down because of that
Yeah, but that's not what I'm here for though
Yeah, I'm just saying don't be doing that because you're gonna get you're gonna get a chill shit down if you do that
Be careful. I'll do that. I've seen other people do that
No, I got what you're saying so I don't I'm not a disagreeing with I've seen that that Jamie Cowboys person
First of all at first. I thought that was a guy and then the person tells me it's a girl
I think that's a person that tied me out there and
Remember we were talking earlier and and Stephanie's chat
Are you talking about sponkeys, right? Sponkeys. Yeah, I went off the panel
I got off the panel and I wrote something in the side chat and that some idiot tied me out. I think it's her
Looks like a guy though. He looks like he looks like a lesbian or really a butch guy a butcher which
Way Sebastian, what do you mean somebody?
Some dyke some dyke called Jamie's Cowboys
that's why I confused it for a guy, but then that person says it was a girl, so alright, fine, anyway, I don't, that person ain't been on the panel either, like another person hides in the side chat, where's the glasses there in the picture, see that, see that picture?
But it looks like a sunglasses, right? Yeah, you can only see like sunglasses in here
But that could be a guy that could be a girl like and then top of the name
The same thing with the name could be a man's name could be a woman's name like the heck man
This person likes to leave people guessing
Yeah, but I don't understand like what's like what is that person doing to make you feel this way?
Because the person time me out earlier and it's always a
Always playing dumb and always condescending it. I know that person's not on my side
So the heck with that person
I don't much like that person and I don't trust that Jamie's
Cowboys person for the record. How do you know wait Sebastian?
How do you know if there's the person that times you out though? It could have been somebody else that
Yeah, you're right. It could be someone else. I just got a doubt that it's her but it could be someone else
I'm not sure. I'm not a hundred percent sure. That's why I'm not saying a hundred percent
Who is awkward then Sebastian? Who is somebody named awkward? I don't know never seen her. Let me see that
Let me look at that picture
Yeah, a nice looking person I never seen that person that person looks good nice looking person
She's actually she says she's actually a really nice lady though
That's what awkward said. I don't think that aqua person would need any liposuction surgery seems to be in good shape
so what do you think about that?
Sebastian
Why accuse them because not accusing I'm saying I think it's you and if it's you just say it's you Jamie
Tell me to choose was it you or not?
Are you playing games with me?
Are you looking to rough on my feathers? I think that Jamie person was trying to rough on my feathers
Earlier what is it? Why did the person Jamie say healing? Thank you T. Why thank you
of the
death of the
And if I do find out it was you the cost will be substantial Jamie and the refund policies will be prohibited not applicable
Yeah, that's just a figure Sebastian
Sebastian, how long are you gonna be like up though for though? Are you gonna be on here for longer?
How much long I don't know man?
Why you want to panel for yourself? I can get off soon if you want if you want to talk on the panel on your own
No, I'm just gonna talk to you though Sebastian or I mean really would talk to
But I could just talk to you though, right? Yeah, I'm not gonna stay on much longer right now
It's like 325, but I don't I don't really gotta go to bed. I just I don't know if I long gonna stay on
Well, you plan on staying on much longer
Who me? Yeah
Wait, wait Sebastian you're talking about me. Yeah, Mason. Yeah, you plan on staying any longer. What do you want to do?
I was thinking about like I mean there's I usually don't stay on panel for that long
This is probably one of the longest times. I've done this I think oh, yeah
You know what I did once once I remember it was a few people around the panel
It was JT and Gotti and me and then they left and then that's like I fell see I say I end up staying on the panel for five
Hours but I'm not gonna do it at this time though. I'm not gonna be staying on the panel that long
I might stay on for another 20 or 30 minutes Sebastian
Sebastian. Yeah
What I normally do when I get on YouTube is watch videos and go to gamer streams and chat to them while they're playing the games
And ask about different video games and how they're doing and they ask me how I'm doing and stuff like that
Check out the game Daytona USA like I told you in Stephanie stream
Yeah, but it's good to talk to those people because you can have a real conversation while they play a game that way could be
Entertained plus talking to them makes you even more entertained if you like that kind of thing
Yeah, if you like that kind of stuff
Yeah
That sounds like fun
Wait, uh Sebastian. I think psych is back on because it's showing psych like awakens and psych awake his terriere on a different one
Yeah, yeah, that's him. I think
Yeah, that's him. Oh, so it's so he's probably back on now, right Sebastian. Yeah, he's probably there backstage somewhere working in the dark
Wait, so we're backstage right now special that's where we are because that's why I don't know where I'm gonna show
He's backstage probably just a figure of speech. He's lurking in the dark there
He's waiting in a wing
Waiting backstage man to see if you'll mess up to see if you'll get out of line
You know, you know, he's waiting to see if you're gonna get out of line or get out of order
Yeah
He's looking to put you in contempt of court
Sebastian don't let it get to you Jamie
What what does Jamie say aqua said don't let it get to you Jamie
That's what Sebastian. That's what somebody said
Hock are you trying to white knife or Jamie? Are you trying to throw me under the bus? Are you trying to ruffle my feathers?
way so Sebastian the thing I don't understand is if you're barely making it how do you even have
time for a cat and how can you afford for a cat like to make it eat and stuff like that if you
don't have enough food for yourself no that's easy I make it a priority I always buy a bag of cat food
and I always make sure I got enough cat food and enough litter box like I got two litter box look
I'm gonna show you I'm gonna throw out my camera look you see those two litter boxes there that's
I'm saying how are you able to do that though with I mean because you know
It's hard enough for you to live on your own to afford for another thing like an animal
It makes it hard. It's important. It's important
You know, I put my cat before me my cat comes first man and a litter box. It's only 10 bucks
It's only 10 bucks for a litter box
It's only 15 bucks for a bag of cats for 25 bucks. I'm gonna make me and gonna put me on the street
You know what I mean, and they're gonna make a difference in my life 25 bucks. I rather put it on her
I I'm gonna starve before my cat stars. That's how much I love my cat my cat ain't never gonna go starving
I always make it a point my child you put yourself Sebastian you put yourself before anybody else right or your cat
I put myself before before my cat sometimes other people, but especially my cat my cat's my child
I gotta take care of her man. She's my responsibility as a father. I gotta take care of my cat
Because I'm her father man, okay, I'm a father my cat now. She's my daughter
You know, she's my baby. That's how I see it because I love my cat. I love her man more than life itself
I ain't lying about that
Yeah, but Sebastian, why do you why would you go for a cat instead of a dog?
Think about it
You can't have a dog in an apartment in Canada here
You can't have a dog in an apartment you can't even find an apartment if you have a dog
They'd say no you right away even a cat
You'll be lucky to rent an apartment if he lets you have a cat because there's laws here man
You can't have an animal you can't have any pets in an apartment building
But here luckily in this apartment building they don't mind that we got cats everyone in the building has a cat pretty much
There's like four out of six people in this building. They got a cat
So best so you are allowed to have a cat there. You're just breaking the rules like just out of course
Of course, I'm allowed man. We're allowed. I you think I didn't ask I asked the owner before I moved
They said I got a cat is that okay? She says yeah
So if your cat doesn't make any noise and you keep things clean, that's fine
Cuz everyone else has a cat in this building except for two people. So that's fine
You just got to take care of your cat you got to keep things clean and put the stuff the litter in a garbage can and stuff
You know what I mean?
Yeah
And what's that noise behind you man? I'm hearing like a noise
What kind of noise you're talking about I hear something you don't hear that either. There's there's a noise behind you. I
Don't hear any noise
No, there's like in there's an echo or is there there's their distortion there
Are you recording me or what man? What's going on there?
Who me? Yeah, you're a distortion like you're recording me or you're you got some noise behind you
I don't know what it is. What's that noise coming from? I
Never heard any noise. It's a best
No, man, it's weird. But anyways, if you record me, I got nothing to hide though
But you see is what you get with me, man. I I keep a hold to what I say, you know what I mean
No, Sebastian, I never was recording man. Don't get it wrong or don't get twisted. You better not
You better not because I'll find you Mason
No, but Sebastian, I'm being real with you man. I'm just kidding. You know if you want to record
I don't care because I got nothing to hide man. You can take everything I say to the bank
No, but Sebastian, I'm just trying to be cool here. I'm not trying to make anything wrong happen or trying to cause any trouble
I know that's fine. That's fine. You're gonna find it. I'm an easy-going guy and I like to joke around
Just don't cross me man. Don't like don't uh, don't backstab me. You know what I mean? I like to joke around
I'm a good guy. I'm an easy-going guy Mason
Yeah, I like joking around. I like laughing. I like joking around
Sebastian, but what do you mean it sounds distorted? I don't hear anything distorted
I think I'm not on your side of the camera. I only hear my side of the
Yeah, that's possible. I just thought I heard I thought I heard something like a distortion. I
Hear from my end. Maybe you don't hear me. I hear from my end, but oh well, there's a matter. Don't worry about it
Okay, there's no noise. Yeah, that's what Jamie says. Yeah, that's fine
I hear though, but anyways, I guess it's a hookup in my phone
What are you doing this week? What are you doing your life? Sebastian? Sebastian. What's gonna go on?
It's gonna go on. What do you mean? Yeah, like what are you gonna do? Like are you just about to go to bed after this?
Yeah, I'm gonna go. I'm gonna go to bed soon. Not just yet. Maybe in an hour
I'm not gonna stay on for long man. I'm gonna stay on maybe another like 20 minutes
If you want the panel for yourself, man, you can have it. I'll let you have the panel for yourself if you want
Wait Sebastian, I don't know what to do right now. The psych is not here
The thing is though once you get off the panel, you can't get back on
Unless he's there if he's there, you can let you back on him. He's not there. You won't be able to get back on
But I think so, what do I do Sebastian? What do I do? I do what you want me
It's up to you to entertain people
With your own brand of entertainment, but don't use any pornography man, that'll mess up the channel
And we'll lose everything is that if you do that don't do that
I'm not gonna know Sebastian. I'm not gonna do that
Some people have done that man some some people like Goddy and some people like other people like Tiffany
They've done that I put some pornography and they got a channel shut down many people have done it people like Vader calls
Myself Mario Billy Hayden Tiffany
AP many people Goddy and JT
Do you know somebody named Zinni?
Yeah, I don't know much, but I know she's done it too. She's probably done it too
Have you ever been to miss fearless souls like YouTube stream? No, I haven't been in there
Her name is her name is Zinnie though. She's the one who runs the show Zinnie Z and why
Yeah, I've heard that person, but I haven't seen her channel though
But is it Vader the one that she always talks about in your streams and stuff like that
She said oh this Vader guy is like a harassing guy a stalker or just some bad guy like a yeah, he's weird
Yeah, he's worth that guy. He's uh, I guess you can say he's a stalker
You I haven't seen you many times like it's one of the first times I've seen you like you came out of nowhere
Are you friends with Ziggy like where'd you come from?
To me
Yeah
No, I'm friends with site. That's how you saw me or what's her name was spunky. You're not friends with Ziggy or IP to
Who is IP to I never heard of that. What's that? Oh, I wasn't sure some other group of people
Wait, so tell me somebody else that you know though Sebastian that I might know
Wait, give me a minute here
Okay
I've whispered just for you
The panel fades
The voices blend
But spirits fire will never end
Story spoken, shadow shown
Seeds of wisdom have been sown
Carry them
Your name
I'll be back in a few minutes
Hey Sike. Yes, yes, Nathan. Where have you been man? I've been spying on you backstage.
It's like I haven't seen you man, like for a while now, like you've been gone, like what happened?
No, I've been just lurking around. What do you mean by lurking around, going to other people's
streams and stuff like that? Sike. No, but I wanted to see if you would notice I was gone.
Yeah, but what what why would you leave those like I thought you wanted to talk to us or be on
Okay
Yeah, we did it's like we did
Yeah, did he tell you what we were talking about I thought you went to bed psych
I thought you fell asleep. Sebastian. What am I Sebastian? Tell me what we were talking about. He wants to know what we were talking about
Well, he heard us he was he heard us when we're talking about
My women right
The best you with Sebastian we were talking about women I think right
We're talking about many things
On the cat. Hey
Oh, Tracy, I was backstage. I was backstage. I know it's rude, but I had to, I had to, I'm sorry. I was just letting them talk.
We were talking about apartments, about jobs, about cats.
We were just talking about stuff.
Many stuff, many things.
I'm just keeping the lights on.
I'm trying to.
Trying to.
Side.
Yes.
Did you see what Jamie said to Sebastian, telling him he wants a free massage or free
liposuction, but Sebastian said no.
Jamie, I don't think you really want that.
Jamie do you want it?
She said okay, and that she didn't time you out. Jamie's my mod. Oh gosh. No, not here
I'm talking about in Stephanie's chat and sparking chat you time it up
All right, I hope not that's what I was saying. I'm not sure I hope it's not her
I hope it's not her because I was telling you that the cost will be substantial the refund balls would be prohibited
It doesn't time people all right
I'll take your word for it. I hope so
Or else she'll pay
But I'll give her the discount on the last I
Don't think she wants it
Well, that's fine too. She doesn't want it. You can always give it to someone else or not
the
Well, yeah, you're not fat man. You don't need the label selection surgery, but other people needed though
Like maybe a family member or a friend that you have
Yeah
It's like
The actually the actually workouts like you do any like
It's his metabolism and Mason he's just meant to be thin
Yeah, what do you do site? Do you actually do workouts or you know for stuff for you?
I just have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this, I have to say this,
No, it's a kind of sad like you know, like I know you Jim nicks going through all this stuff
And then like people are paying on Sam and so they have a picture put up
diaper
Her close-up on her teeth and stuff like that like right and she's like
going to like doctor's appointments for like, you know, really serious thing
Some people need help some people got serious problems mentally
Some people
Most people in this country, I mean it's like, you know, it's like a sick society
It's a sick society. All right, Patrick. That's true
There's weird people out there, thank you. Yeah, but it's like people
Look at like some of the changes
Like yes
Do you have any soda, man? Do you drink any soda? I wish I did
Actually, I have a couple of my clothes I might drink
You got any soda, maybe energy drinks like are those energy drinks?
You know what you got any drinks there Mason no, I mean not with me, but I haven't been a kitchen though
Sebastian look what I have. This is good. I have a watermelon white claw
Hey, Sebastian
Hello
Yeah, I see that
Sebastian
Yeah
Do you have any sodas to drink man? Oh, I got nothing right now. I'm dead broke. I
Got nothing I tell you
I put water in balls of water. I put in the fridge man cold balls of water
Oh balls of water it costs nothing it's free
That's when you're poor. That's the best thing to do Mason when you're poor
You're gonna put water in bottles put in the fridge nice cold balls of water real refreshing
No, I fill them up with tap water with the water from the fuss and then it gets cold after a few hours
You got cold balls of water cost nothing
You got to fill up the same bottles you got to keep some bottles and you fill them up
You know what I mean? You put them in the fridge. It costs you nothing
Sebastian, why is it costing nothing?
Well, don't you get it man? That's how you save money you were talking earlier
How do you get buying life? That's I you can save money by doing that keeping bottles and you put water in them
You put them in the fridge that gives you cold balls of water instead of buying soda and drinks gots a fortune
Yeah, everything cost is everything's expensive these days. You might as well like save money when you can you you got put water in the fridge
You know, I mean
Yeah
Sebastian why won't you show yourself again? You still want women to get track teams. I don't want women to get turned on
I'm not looking at like like, you know, I'm trying to keep it family oriented and I don't want to like for privacy purposes
Yeah, cuz I got a huge fan club, and I gotta be careful. You know, you can never be too careful around some people
I got a very huge fan club if you see what I'm cooking. I
Mean some of the women out there like people like like Anna and Jamie and other people like they might get turned on
I'm not looking at I'm not looking to distract them. It's I want to take the attention off Patrick here
Because it's like show I don't want to take the attention off psych
I
Actually like the rock like the rest are named the rock. I like the rock, but I like Stone Cold Steve Austin even better
But you said do you spell what you're cooking that's what the rock says though. Yeah, I like him. I like I like Kane
Remember that guy Kane
No, the big big red machine remember that big tall guy with a red suit the big red machine
Yeah
the
I met those guys I saw them in person back in 2000. They were coming out of the building. It was in the garage. I
Saw them in person like right on the street. I walked right up to their car. I got a picture of him
Sebastian what about the undertaker do you like the undertaker? Yeah, he's okay, but I prefer came I prefer came
What about the big show Sebastian the big show yeah, he's all right
I remember Jerry the king luller on commentary and jr. Remember those guys
commentary
Yeah
Sebastian, what do you think about Michael Cole and Taz when they were I don't like them I don't like them too much
I prefer a Jerry the king luller and jr
This this raw team not to smack down team like right
But the vietta 2 era from 97 to like 2001. That's when it was good
Yeah, but have you watched like the smackdown commentators, you know how the raw commentators are
JR and
Jerry King waller
Yeah, yeah, okay
Ha these idiots
These idiots like Tony there in the side jet got no lives like to lie about people say these things that aren't true
Watch your cowards. I tell you bunch of faggots and carrots
Hey site yeah
So were you sleeping earlier? That's why you weren't on here. Did you accidentally fall asleep or what?
No, I was just
Watching from backstage. It was lurking. I told you never I told you that he was lurking bro. He was watching
Why were you watching from backstage to us like you wanted Sebastian not just to talk for a while. Yeah
I want to see how you interact with
Sometimes it's nice for the host to take a break. He only just wants to sit back and let the guests talk
You want to see if you'd mess up, you know, you want to see if you'd conduct yourself properly
What do you mean by see if I messed up though
You want to see if you'd be you behave appropriately and getting to conduct yourself properly
I thought that's what I was doing those best. Oh, you did you did well
Did good you did good Mason
So so so that means work so that means we're cool though like right Sebastian. Yeah. Oh, yeah
As a matter of fact, he did so well, you know what Mason? I think I'm gonna give you the award for outstanding achievement in the field of excellence
what
Well, I'm giving you that award the outstanding the award for outstanding achievement in the field of excellence. I
Don't know what that means though. It means you you gave a good performance. It means you know
You you had outstanding achievement in the field of excellence
His performance on the panel he was he did good. He did good. He did well
I
Even told him I said don't don't do any pornography now. Well, he's not there. You know I warned him. I told him not to do that
In case you know
Did you ever did you ever get any pornography before site?
I love you guys
The rest of the evening, I'm just going to kind of, yeah, take almost one in the morning to get some rest and stuff.
Let's have a great week, guys. Thank you for the one for supporting the night, and we had, this was pretty fun.
Thank you so much for being here. Check out secondyweekends.com. I do have a book available.
Is that true, Hannah? Is that true that that hailed person, that's Gotti?
Sebastian, when do you come on here though, man? So like I could see you. Yeah, Hannah is that true? You're just just guessing here speculating
I'd like to talk to this hand on the panel one-on-one one of these days
It's us it's us Sebastian Hannah says all these panels guess are unbearable
I know then she's got the wrong attitude man. Maybe she's jealous, but she's got the wrong attitude though
We're very cocky soon
From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight, truce get told, it goes unfold.
Trolls be dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
It's like we awake, can't step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so deep play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like we awake, can't stop look away
Your shadow's talking, it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream live from the madness, this ain't no dream